<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xml:space="preserve" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0 https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kermitt2/grobid/master/grobid-home/schemas/xsd/Grobid.xsd">
	<teiHeader xml:lang="en">
		<fileDesc>
			<titleStmt>
				<title level="a" type="main"/>
			</titleStmt>
			<publicationStmt>
				<publisher/>
				<availability status="unknown"><licence/></availability>
			</publicationStmt>
			<sourceDesc>
				<biblStruct>
					<analytic>
					</analytic>
					<monogr>
						<imprint>
							<date/>
						</imprint>
					</monogr>
					<idno type="MD5">44821AD1918F7A47C0284D1760C498AE</idno>
				</biblStruct>
			</sourceDesc>
		</fileDesc>
		<encodingDesc>
			<appInfo>
				<application version="0.8.1" ident="GROBID" when="2024-11-22T09:43+0000">
					<desc>GROBID - A machine learning software for extracting information from scholarly documents</desc>
					<ref target="https://github.com/kermitt2/grobid"/>
				</application>
			</appInfo>
		</encodingDesc>
		<profileDesc>
			<abstract>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="2,77.01,33.84,102.53,24.02">Takeaways</head><p><s coords="2,101.78,177.79,305.02,10.08">• The two main ways of EV battery recycling are reuse and direct recycle.</s><s coords="2,408.33,177.79,489.13,10.08;2,115.94,189.79,264.72,10.08">The large-scale development of reuse faces enormous challenges due to safety issues, insufficient market regulation, the impact of vicious competition, and the lack of industry standards.</s><s coords="2,382.44,189.79,510.17,10.08;2,115.94,201.79,82.37,10.08">In the medium-to long-term, recycle with relatively mature technologies and commercial applications is expected to be the dominant approach</s></p><p><s coords="2,101.78,219.79,781.77,10.08;2,115.94,231.82,756.95,10.08;2,115.94,243.82,179.62,10.08">• In the material recovery process, pyro-and hydro-metallurgy are the mainstream battery-grade raw material purification and regeneration techniques, which has high technical and scale barriers, while creating higher economic benefits, leading companies need to address the supply stability of front-end battery recycling channels and actively layout raw material recycling capacity to achieve higher commercial value</s></p><p><s coords="2,36.91,77.50,595.95,11.04">With the rapid growth of global new energy vehicle industry, the upstream resource constraint has become one of the burning issues.</s><s coords="2,635.12,77.50,260.13,11.04;2,36.91,90.70,882.71,11.04;2,36.91,103.88,148.19,11.06">While various countries continue to perfect the EV battery recycling policy system under the carbon neutral requirements, the EV battery recycling industry has been flourishing, and the upcoming battery retirement tide will further drive the development of the EV battery recycling industry.</s><s coords="2,187.35,103.88,701.39,11.06">The EV battery recycling market is promising in technology development, business model, and industry chain synergy, but there are still many key challenges.</s></p><p><s coords="2,101.78,430.03,780.15,10.08;2,115.94,442.03,273.91,10.08">• Upstream lithium and new energy vehicle industry technology and market trends, such as battery material innovation, integration technology, battery banks, etc., bring impact to the power battery recycling industry, and opportunities and challenges coexist</s></p><p><s coords="2,101.78,460.03,793.73,10.08;2,115.94,472.01,189.46,10.10">• An industry alliance of upstream and downstream enterprises in the industry chain may be an ideal model for the recycling industry, as each member enterprise can complement each other's strengths and weaknesses for mutual benefits.</s><s coords="2,307.16,472.01,599.41,10.10">However, due to the long industry chain and many stakeholders involved, the model is still in the exploration stage of actual commercial operation</s></p><p><s coords="2,102.55,139.49,586.25,12.00">From the technology development perspective, the process and technical route of EV battery recycling is relatively clear.</s><s coords="2,691.90,139.49,193.73,12.00;2,102.55,153.89,392.84,12.00">Based on actual business expectations, direct recycle will dominate the recovery method in the medium-to long-term:</s></p><p><s coords="2,102.55,276.58,548.65,12.02">From the business model perspective, third-party and battery manufacturer recycling have been well-practiced.</s><s coords="2,654.46,276.58,214.13,12.02;2,102.55,291.02,267.44,12.00">The construction of recycling networks and closed-loop regeneration are essential success factors:</s></p><p><s coords="2,102.55,392.71,789.58,12.00;2,102.55,407.14,150.24,12.00">From the industry chain synergy perspective, the multiple sectors of the Li-battery and NEV industry chain have shown the trend of extending to battery recycling in different forms and degrees:</s></p><p><s coords="2,101.78,314.28,473.06,10.08">• The market mechanism is the main challenge for the current development of the EV battery recycling industry.</s><s coords="2,576.37,314.28,298.12,10.08;2,115.94,326.26,144.21,10.10">It forces the leading recycler enterprises to enhance their scale and break through the profitability bottleneck</s></p><p><s coords="2,101.78,345.74,792.20,10.08;2,115.94,360.14,766.86,10.08">• Third-party recycling companies have the advantage of recycling technology, while battery manufacturers and automotive OEMs gained the advantage of recycling and resale channels; in the current EV battery recycling market, the key to successful business models lies in the construction of recycling channel networks and a closed-loop ecology for recycling materials for reuse</s></p></div>
			</abstract>
		</profileDesc>
	</teiHeader>
	<facsimile>
		<surface n="1" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="2" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="3" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="4" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="5" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="6" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="7" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="8" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="9" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="10" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="11" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="12" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="13" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="14" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="15" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="16" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="17" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="18" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="19" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="20" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="21" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="22" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="23" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="24" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="25" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="26" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="27" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="28" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="29" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="30" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="31" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="32" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="33" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
		<surface n="34" ulx="0.0" uly="0.0" lrx="957.6" lry="538.56"/>
	</facsimile>
	<text xml:lang="en">
		<body>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="4,35.16,222.54,595.40,43.94;4,35.16,275.37,375.37,43.94">Industry overview and prospects of EV battery recycle</head><p><s coords="5,36.91,33.84,868.30,24.02">The Imperative EV Battery Recycling: Alleviation to The Constraint of Upstream Resources</s></p><p><s coords="5,36.91,73.64,657.62,13.94">The scarcity of upstream resources is a long-term constraint to the development of downstream application market.</s><s coords="5,698.18,73.64,182.30,13.94;5,36.91,90.48,740.03,13.92">The lithium resource supply and demand gap is expected to emerge and expand gradually after 2025, reaching 145 tonnes of lithium carbonate equivalent in 2030.</s><s coords="5,780.62,90.48,135.32,13.92;5,36.91,107.28,636.55,13.92">EV battery recycling will alleviate the constraints of resource supply and demand imbalance on industry development to a certain extent.</s></p><p><s coords="5,36.07,486.61,239.58,7.92;5,75.60,134.95,149.08,13.92;5,727.42,133.92,160.75,13.94">Source: CAAM, Minmetals Securities, public information, Deloitte analysis Supply: resource pressure Demand: surging EV market</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="5,75.62,167.54,134.45,12.00">Resource shortage in China</head><p><s coords="5,75.62,180.26,153.54,11.04;5,75.62,192.24,113.41,11.06">High-quality mineral resources are relatively scarce in China.</s><s coords="5,191.02,192.24,62.39,11.06;5,75.62,204.05,182.81,11.04;5,75.62,216.05,188.35,11.04;5,75.62,227.81,169.18,11.04;5,75.62,239.79,103.60,11.06">There are few high-quality hard rock lithium mines, and the technology and production capacity of lithium extraction from salt-lake brine require breakthroughs.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="5,75.62,272.50,174.68,12.00">Uncertainty of international supply</head><p><s coords="5,75.62,285.22,161.89,11.04;5,75.62,297.22,150.74,11.04;5,75.62,308.98,76.18,11.04">The supply of global raw materials is concentrated, and the production fluctuates wildly.</s><s coords="5,153.81,308.98,108.89,11.04;5,75.62,320.96,160.61,11.06;5,75.62,332.76,177.26,11.04;5,75.62,344.76,170.23,11.04">Emergencies such as the epidemic outbreak and the Russian-Ukrainian conflict have exacerbated the uncertainty of the global supply chain.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="5,75.62,377.42,163.57,12.00">Long capacity development cycle</head><p><s coords="5,75.62,390.14,178.70,11.04;5,75.62,402.12,135.22,11.06">The development cycle of raw materials and minerals is relatively long.</s><s coords="5,213.08,402.12,16.55,11.06;5,75.62,413.93,172.74,11.04;5,75.62,425.93,180.85,11.04;5,75.62,437.69,158.54,11.04;5,75.62,449.67,178.46,11.06">The resource production expansion cycle is about four times that of the EV batteries expansion cycle, thus leading to the mismatch between supply and demand.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="5,733.30,167.54,134.93,12.00">Strong application demand</head><p><s coords="5,733.30,180.26,174.17,11.04;5,733.30,192.24,187.49,11.06;5,733.30,204.05,172.48,11.04;5,733.30,216.05,186.85,11.04;5,733.30,227.81,145.82,11.04">The EV market, as the main application scenario of lithium resources, has entered a period of rapid growth, and the sales volume of EVs in China increased by more than 150% year-on-year in 2021.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="5,733.30,266.45,139.71,12.02">Difficulty in alternative R&amp;D</head><p><s coords="5,733.30,279.22,171.64,11.04;5,733.30,291.22,109.23,11.04">The R&amp;D of EV batteries with different chemicals is challenging.</s><s coords="5,844.30,291.22,68.02,11.04;5,733.30,302.98,182.08,11.04;5,733.30,314.96,186.89,11.06;5,733.30,326.76,166.03,11.04;5,733.30,338.76,167.59,11.04">In the long run, Li-batteries, which have a relatively fixed demand for mineral resources, will still be the mainstay, and it is hard to find an alternative solution in the short term.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="5,733.30,377.42,108.82,12.00">Intensive competition</head><p><s coords="5,733.30,390.14,182.29,11.04;5,733.30,402.12,174.27,11.06;5,733.30,413.93,188.68,11.04;5,733.30,425.93,182.84,11.04;5,733.30,437.81,101.22,10.56">Battery companies maintain a rapid pace of expansion to seize market share and drive the demand for upstream resources, amid the increasingly fierce competition in the EV battery industry.</s></p><p><s coords="5,323.35,141.87,314.65,13.94;5,403.06,158.47,155.32,13.92">Global lithium resource supply and demand projection (Ten thousand tonnes/LCE)</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,37.13,162.04,109.39,18.00;7,221.47,162.04,52.94,18.00;7,759.48,314.02,111.92,11.04">North America Europe MIIT and other six 2018</head><p><s coords="7,759.48,332.68,138.74,7.92;7,759.48,342.28,133.66,7.92;7,759.48,351.88,136.38,7.92">Implementation of the extended producer responsibility system, clarify the primary responsibility fulfillers of battery recycling</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,574.66,223.63,117.70,11.04">MIIT and other two 2022</head><p><s coords="7,574.66,242.29,147.81,7.92;7,574.66,251.89,154.19,7.92;7,574.66,261.47,101.44,7.94">To develop and introduce new energy vehicle power battery recycling management methods and related departmental rules</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,574.32,306.14,126.34,11.04">MIIT and other seven 2022</head><p><s coords="7,574.32,324.80,129.89,7.92;7,574.32,334.40,136.38,7.92;7,574.32,343.98,58.98,7.94">To promote upstream and downstream cooperation in the industry chain to build recycling channels</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,759.48,223.56,50.48,11.04">MIIT 2020</head><p><s coords="7,759.48,242.22,145.24,7.92;7,759.48,251.80,130.24,7.94;7,759.48,261.44,132.49,7.92;7,759.48,271.04,143.01,7.92;7,759.48,280.64,28.76,7.92">To promote the NEV power battery recycling system development, and to establish a number of exemplary enterprises for the secondary use and recycling of waste power batteries</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,570.67,161.68,42.03,18.02">China</head><p><s coords="7,71.54,137.54,455.84,12.00">Policy and legislative systems in developed countries started early and are relatively mature</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,759.48,396.10,50.48,11.04">MIIT 2018</head><p><s coords="7,759.48,414.76,136.14,7.92;7,759.48,424.36,114.92,7.92;7,759.48,433.94,127.71,7.94;7,759.48,443.58,137.12,7.92;7,572.76,450.44,143.58,7.92;7,572.76,460.99,94.96,7.94">Establish a "comprehensive management platform for traceability" to collect information on the whole process from production to recycling of power batteries The Management Standards for New Energy Storage Projects (Provisional)</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,574.94,390.12,48.80,11.04">NEA 2021</head><p><s coords="7,574.94,408.78,157.27,7.92;7,574.94,418.36,149.33,7.94;7,574.94,428.00,135.95,7.92;7,574.94,437.60,136.61,7.92">Request for establishing the battery consistency management, and make requirements for the evaluation, monitoring and supervision of energy storage projects for secondary use</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,37.13,190.37,150.87,11.04;7,37.13,203.55,130.75,11.06">Complete federal, state and local battery recycling regulations</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,220.99,190.16,128.70,11.06;7,220.99,203.40,138.89,11.04">Enhanced requirements and strengthen regulatory systems</head><p><s coords="7,573.67,190.15,346.14,11.04;7,573.67,203.35,172.26,11.04">Gradually improve the establishment of the policy system to strengthen the regulation and policy implementation</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,587.26,137.54,308.06,12.00">China's policy guidance has been strengthened in recent years</head><p><s coords="7,40.32,303.23,164.61,7.94">National Blueprint for Lithium Batteries 2021-2030</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,223.49,223.37,42.08,11.04">EU 2022</head><p><s coords="7,223.49,242.03,153.09,7.92;7,223.49,251.63,153.50,7.92;7,223.49,261.25,137.57,7.92;7,223.49,270.85,153.99,7.92;7,223.49,280.45,16.58,7.92;7,223.32,292.02,143.34,7.92">The proposed battery regulations set increased targets related to power battery recycling, with stricter requirements for battery recycling measures and battery metal material recovery rates New EU Regulatory Framework for Batteries</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,223.42,403.46,74.00,11.04">Germany 2021</head><p><s coords="7,223.42,422.12,141.94,7.92;7,223.42,431.70,118.95,7.94;7,223.42,441.35,161.69,7.92;7,223.42,450.95,156.65,7.92;7,223.42,460.55,102.71,7.92;7,221.35,471.88,22.73,7.92">Regulatory agencies (Stiftung EAR) have the responsibility to regulate the battery manufacturing market and to check the collection and recycling efficiency of each recycling system and report market participation BattG2</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,401.66,389.62,89.15,11.04">Diet of Japan 2001</head><p><s coords="7,401.66,408.28,141.54,7.92;7,401.66,417.88,144.84,7.92;7,401.66,427.48,141.41,7.92;7,401.66,437.06,151.20,7.94;7,401.66,446.70,46.04,7.92">Manufacturing enterprises should fulfill the responsibility of recycling the used products, follow the 3R principle, and encourage that end-users send end-of-life batteries to special recycling sites</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,401.71,306.74,134.99,11.04">The Ministries of Japan 2004</head><p><s coords="7,401.71,325.40,133.53,7.92;7,401.71,335.00,146.44,7.92;7,401.71,344.60,154.43,7.92;7,401.71,354.18,120.52,7.94;7,401.71,363.83,101.88,7.92">The Japan Portable Rechargeable Battery Recycling Center (JBRC), jointly authorized by Japan's two central ministries, aims to promote the comprehensive recycling of used rechargeable battery materials</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,41.76,225.12,89.14,11.04">The U.S. DOE 2021</head><p><s coords="7,41.76,243.78,139.52,7.92;7,41.76,253.38,145.98,7.92;7,41.76,262.98,116.18,7.92;7,41.76,272.56,146.68,7.94;7,41.76,282.20,127.72,7.92;7,41.76,291.80,98.35,7.92">Enables the end-of-life reuse of lithium-ion batteries and recycling of critical materials at scale, plan the construction of a full competitive value chain in the United States, and promote the development of costeffective recycling technology</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,223.32,318.38,85.54,11.04">Switzerland 2022</head><p><s coords="7,223.32,337.04,153.33,7.92;7,223.32,346.64,153.49,7.92;7,223.32,356.24,157.39,7.92;7,223.32,365.87,141.56,7.92;7,223.32,375.47,50.92,7.92;7,221.33,386.94,69.52,7.92">Guide to Waste issued by the Federal Office for Environmental clarify rules for recycling lithium batteries for vehicles and encourage automotive OEMs to implement environmentally sound disposal system FOEN Guide to Waste</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,401.71,223.44,150.83,11.04">South Korean's Parliament 2021</head><p><s coords="7,401.71,242.10,154.77,7.92;7,401.71,251.70,149.23,7.92;7,401.71,261.28,140.80,7.94;7,401.71,270.92,150.21,7.92;7,401.71,280.52,76.47,7.92;7,41.50,327.17,89.84,11.04;7,41.50,345.83,124.99,7.92;7,41.50,355.43,151.66,7.92;7,41.50,365.01,146.79,7.94;7,41.50,374.65,94.10,7.92">Ease regulation for mandatory battery recycling of previously registered vehicles and allow for environmental-friendly utilize of end-of-life batteries to improve the secondary utilization rate of power batteries The U.S. EPA 1996 Creates the framework for the proper management of hazardous and non-hazardous solid waste, including rechargeable batteries, lithium-ion car batteries, etc.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="7,39.29,389.03,145.30,7.94">The Resource Conservation and Recovery Act</head><p><s coords="7,41.50,414.12,127.87,11.04">The U.S. State Governments</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="8,37.13,168.17,24.53,12.00">GWh</head><p><s coords="8,45.62,426.67,508.17,11.04">• With the vigorous development of the global EV market, the installed capacity of EV batteries has risen rapidly.</s><s coords="8,555.80,426.67,219.71,11.04">The service life of EV batteries is about 5-8 years.</s><s coords="8,777.76,426.67,123.80,11.04;8,59.78,439.87,827.74,11.04">Therefore, the first batch of batteries put into the market has ushered in a "retirement tide", especially in the Chinese market, where the production output and sales of EVs and EV batteries have soared since 2015.</s><s coords="8,45.62,455.98,357.52,11.04">• End-of-life batteries are the primary "raw materials" for EV battery recycling.</s><s coords="8,405.40,455.98,507.86,11.04">The advent of the EV battery retirement tide will continue to provide recyclable waste for the Li-battery recycling.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="9,823.85,269.78,43.40,11.04">Electrolyt</head><p><s coords="9,823.85,284.42,52.75,11.04;9,823.85,298.80,86.62,11.06;9,598.25,339.94,308.10,11.04;9,524.78,351.94,161.58,11.04;9,511.34,366.03,377.44,11.59;9,524.78,378.56,367.81,11.06">Recycled by extracting methods The process is more straightforward than reuse, and there is no need for screening and safety assessment ＋ Complementary techniques: a combined approach can be applied to improve the economic benefits of recycling and solve the problem of energy over-consumption</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="9,559.85,263.52,71.63,11.04">Other materials</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="10,657.74,296.02,81.10,9.12">Battery reuse process</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="10,678.34,376.42,116.97,9.12">Key technical difficulties sectors</head><p><s coords="10,43.68,153.50,265.45,9.12">• The reuse industry management system still needs to be improved:</s></p><p><s coords="10,57.12,164.30,251.94,9.12;10,57.12,175.10,241.66,9.12;10,57.12,185.88,194.25,9.14">The policy management system for the reuse of EV batteries is still in the initial stage of establishment, and it takes time to improve the national regulatory system and local implementation</s></p><p><s coords="10,43.68,199.85,265.46,9.12;10,57.12,210.65,216.50,9.12;10,57.12,221.45,245.40,9.12;10,57.12,232.25,250.51,9.12">• Policy guidance maintains a moderately positive attitude: Although the policy intends to promote reuse, it also emphasizes the importance of strict management of the safety of EV battery reuse, and is especially cautious towards reuse in energy storage scenarios.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="10,59.76,250.44,29.82,9.12">2022.02</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="10,57.10,260.92,229.75,7.92;10,57.10,271.48,32.86,7.92">Accelerating the Promotion of Comprehensive Utilization of Industrial Resources</head><p><s coords="10,57.10,285.14,243.22,7.94;10,57.10,295.74,245.66,7.92;10,57.10,306.30,245.93,7.92;10,57.10,316.86,233.05,7.92">Requirements to improve the recycling system and management system of end-of-life power batteries, strengthen traceability management within the whole life cycle of battery, promote the safe reuse application of end-of-life power batteries in the field of power backup, charging and replacement</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="10,57.10,344.00,245.63,7.92">The Management Standards for New Energy Storage Projects (Provisional)</head><p><s coords="10,57.10,357.44,251.56,7.92;10,57.10,368.00,233.31,7.92;10,57.10,378.56,247.64,7.92">Require newly-built energy storage projects to establish a battery consistency management and traceability systems and obtain the safety assessment reports issued by corresponding qualified organization for reuse of batteries</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="10,59.78,329.81,29.85,9.14">2021.09</head><p><s coords="10,343.39,153.50,130.45,9.12">Demand side -uncertain potential:</s></p><p><s coords="10,343.39,164.30,272.16,9.12;10,356.86,175.10,258.21,9.12;10,356.86,185.88,199.80,9.14">• Low acceptance in the downstream market: Due to unclear standards and immature regulatory system, frequent accidents of battery reused for energy storage have led to low market acceptance.</s><s coords="10,557.96,185.88,34.29,9.14;10,356.86,196.73,232.58,9.12;10,343.39,207.53,249.42,9.12;10,356.86,218.33,231.67,9.12;10,356.86,229.13,198.09,9.12;10,343.39,243.07,162.41,9.12">Users are concerned about the safety and consistency of reused batteries • Impact of potential alternative products: the rise of sodium-ion batteries and fuel cells and other technologies may replace and squeeze the market of LFP batteries for secondary use Supply side -"bad money drives out good":</s></p><p><s coords="10,343.39,253.87,236.09,9.12;10,356.86,264.67,238.92,9.12;10,356.86,275.47,253.43,9.12;10,356.86,286.27,236.39,9.12">• Long-standing market confusion: In the absence of effective regulation, many non-compliant small workshops have long been entrenched in the reuse market, and it is difficult for enterprises with high investments to profit and survive in the vicious competition</s></p><p><s coords="11,36.91,73.64,879.78,13.94;11,36.91,90.48,356.18,13.92">The main challenge of power battery dismantling and recycling lies in the instability of front-end battery recycling channels that make it difficult to scale up the production of back-end battery grade raw material refining</s></p><p><s coords="11,36.91,33.84,420.64,24.02;11,36.50,488.12,143.57,7.92">Recycle: Process Flow of EV Battery Recycle Source: public information, Deloitte analysis</s></p><p><s coords="11,44.30,430.49,270.55,10.08;11,44.30,442.51,276.29,10.08;11,44.30,454.51,285.40,10.08;11,44.30,466.51,138.01,10.08">The instability and high cost due to the highly-fragmented battery recycling channels, and the difficulties of pretreatment due to wide range of battery pack specifications are the two main difficulties in the disassembly and recycling process</s></p><p><s coords="11,358.30,430.70,542.56,10.08;11,358.30,442.70,541.73,10.08;11,358.30,454.70,507.21,10.08;11,358.30,466.69,125.82,10.10">The mechanical process and the metal refining process after the pretreatment of the battery pack have been relatively mature, can realize the effective conversion of the end-of-life EV batteries to recyclable high-purity raw materials; in the situation of sharply-rising lithium metal raw material prices, large-scale production, stable supply of end-of-life batteries and client relations can realize considerable economic returns</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="11,871.27,161.91,27.09,11.06">Li Salt</head><p><s coords="11,869.11,205.42,31.39,11.04">Cu Salt</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="11,869.83,250.51,29.71,11.04">Ni Salt</head><p><s coords="11,867.19,295.58,35.23,11.04">Mn Salt</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="11,864.55,340.68,40.30,11.04;11,860.33,383.35,48.95,11.04;11,867.53,393.91,34.49,11.04">Graphite Electrolyte Solvent</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="11,102.74,323.66,40.20,11.04">Used cell</head><p><s coords="11,70.63,212.66,104.82,11.04">End-of-life battery pack</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="11,269.69,275.04,63.02,12.00;11,251.93,289.44,98.21,12.00">Dismantling, shredding &amp; sorting</head><p><s coords="11,666.79,280.61,87.51,12.00">Hydro-metallurgy</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="11,577.03,182.30,80.04,12.00">Pyro-metallurgy</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="11,51.12,228.12,69.17,12.00;11,55.22,242.54,60.60,12.00">Discharging &amp; disassembly</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="11,583.80,386.95,99.23,12.00">Electrolyte recovery</head><p><s coords="11,267.31,388.18,73.14,11.04">Used electrolyte</s></p><p><s coords="11,373.58,354.43,114.70,12.00">Plastics, Cu/Al foils etc.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="11,79.42,352.39,109.58,11.04">Typical recycling process</head><p><s coords="11,79.39,370.01,74.88,11.06">Optional process</s></p><p><s coords="11,79.39,387.70,79.28,11.04">Recycling product</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="11,457.49,124.87,310.19,13.92;11,248.57,124.82,113.31,13.92;11,85.78,126.50,77.55,13.92">Battery-grade Materials Extraction &amp; Refining Process Mechanical Process Pretreatment</head><p><s coords="11,499.20,301.92,48.70,11.04;11,461.74,315.31,29.40,11.04">Black mass (incl.</s><s coords="11,493.39,315.86,92.21,11.04">Li, Ni, Cu, Mn, etc.)</s></p><p><s coords="12,576.17,189.08,288.06,10.10;12,589.61,201.84,301.53,10.08;12,589.61,214.56,51.93,10.08">• Use high-temperature to convert metal oxides end-of-life in battery materials to metals or metal compounds, which proceeds to condensation and refining.</s><s coords="12,643.07,214.56,236.25,10.08;12,589.61,227.28,208.73,10.08">Pyro has high compatibility and is applicable to large-scale recycling of various types of end-of-life Li-batteries.</s></p><p><s coords="12,199.20,191.76,316.96,10.08;12,212.64,203.76,284.51,10.08;12,212.64,215.76,265.68,10.08">• Use acids to dissolve the metal components of batteries and then separate the constituent elements as inorganic salts and metallic oxide through solvent extractions, chemical precipitation, and electrolysis steps.</s><s coords="12,480.57,215.76,33.22,10.08;12,212.64,227.76,296.57,10.08">Hydro is suitable for the recycling of small and medium-scale end-of-life batteries.</s></p><p><s coords="12,36.91,73.64,873.81,13.94;12,36.91,90.48,489.73,13.92;13,471.22,400.40,405.65,11.06">Recycling enterprises generally refine the valuable metals in end-of-life EV batteries through hydro or pyro-metallurgy, which are highly-technical maturity and with clear steps, while other emerging processes, such as biological processes and The development of NMC batteries starts later than LFP, and the recovery rate also lagged.</s><s coords="13,878.63,400.40,32.87,11.06;13,471.22,414.36,200.71,11.04">End-oflife LFP batteries are more suitable for reuse.</s><s coords="13,674.41,414.36,207.42,11.04;13,471.22,428.28,339.30,11.04">However, reuse has not yet achieved technical breakthroughs currently, and it is challenging to achieve economies of scale.</s><s coords="13,813.05,428.28,101.91,11.04;13,471.22,442.44,394.88,11.04">It is projected that the recycling market of NMC batteries will continue to lead in the short and medium term.</s></p><p><s coords="13,46.13,400.27,386.95,11.04;13,60.31,413.47,138.44,11.04;13,46.13,429.55,380.98,11.04;13,60.31,442.78,167.86,11.04">• LFP batteries are more suitable for reusing due to their relatively low material cost, good stability and long lifespan • NMC batteries are more suitable for recycling due to their relatively high material cost, poor stability and short lifespan.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="13,82.66,283.39,40.79,11.04">Cycle life</head><p><s coords="13,140.18,271.71,121.51,10.10;13,140.18,283.75,130.34,10.08;13,140.18,295.75,25.66,10.08">The average cycle life is about 4,000, and the capacity declines slowly</s></p><p><s coords="13,296.06,277.75,138.73,10.08;13,296.06,289.75,94.65,10.08">The average cycle life is estimated at 2,000 times or lower</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="13,86.02,319.97,34.03,11.06;13,88.90,333.22,28.00,11.04">Battery safety</head><p><s coords="13,140.18,314.95,102.72,10.08;13,140.18,326.93,134.15,10.10;13,140.18,338.98,119.56,10.08;13,296.06,314.95,138.04,10.08;13,296.06,326.93,141.31,10.10;13,296.06,338.98,68.52,10.08;15,665.18,270.62,182.14,12.00;15,678.62,284.76,211.03,11.06;15,678.62,298.01,220.48,11.04;15,678.62,311.21,185.05,11.04;15,678.62,324.41,213.75,11.04;15,678.62,337.59,76.44,11.06">More stable, less likely to experience thermal runaway and ignition at high temperatures At abnormally high temperatures, the possibility of fire and explosion is relatively large  • Resource-based extension: Battery enterprises, OEMs and battery banks and other power exchange service companies are predicted to take advantage of resources to expand downwards into the recycling and establishing a recycling system.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="14,35.16,222.54,363.77,43.94;14,35.16,275.37,375.37,43.94">Value chain analysis of EV battery recycle</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="15,665.18,383.93,223.59,13.94;15,665.18,400.78,75.60,13.92">Battery recycling enterprises extend to other sectors</head><p><s coords="15,665.18,422.86,199.53,11.04;15,678.62,436.06,213.46,11.04;15,678.62,449.24,216.56,11.06;15,678.62,462.48,211.98,11.04">• Through dismantling end-of-life batteries, recycling enterprises are likely to expand to raw materials, cathode materials manufacturing etc., forming a closed loop within the industry chain.</s><s coords="18,722.59,365.14,143.43,10.08;18,722.59,377.14,146.29,10.08;18,722.59,389.12,173.39,10.10;18,722.59,401.16,159.64,10.08">The company builds a collaborative recycling industry chain system, and upgrades its business from waste recycling to new energy material manufacturing.</s><s coords="18,722.59,413.16,138.37,10.08;18,722.59,425.16,162.65,10.08;18,722.59,437.14,129.37,10.10">The revenue share of new energy material manufacturing increased from 26.5% in 2016 to 71.1% in 2021</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="15,456.96,340.32,95.16,10.08">Battery Manufacturing</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="15,349.56,471.01,88.16,10.10;15,171.94,470.86,159.35,10.08">OEM &amp; Consumption Battery Charging &amp; Replacing Facilities</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="15,85.25,340.32,42.62,10.08;15,81.17,353.04,50.71,10.08">Resources Exploitation</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="15,196.27,213.55,56.16,10.08;15,179.47,226.27,89.91,10.08">Raw Material Refining &amp; Processing</head><p><s coords="18,508.70,249.89,390.22,10.08;18,508.70,262.61,205.18,10.08">In order to create a closed-loop value chain for the entire life-cycle of EV batteries, the company has tackled many technical challenges in recycling.</s><s coords="18,715.18,262.61,177.04,10.08;18,508.70,275.33,394.30,10.08;18,508.70,288.03,379.87,10.10;18,508.70,300.79,212.05,10.08">It is working to ensure the safety of the raw material supply system for new energy material recycling, address the urgent need for the supply chain of critical new energy raw materials, and realize the recycling and deep processing from waste to raw materials for high-end brand products.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="18,95.86,217.75,311.96,12.00">KSF 1: Secured resource channels and strong recycling network</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="18,63.89,379.22,77.39,10.08">Car manufacturers</head><p><s coords="18,55.32,252.98,389.84,10.08;18,55.32,265.70,389.04,10.08;18,55.32,278.45,320.31,10.08">Through deepened collaborative development of the industrial chain, the company continues to expand its recycling and resale channels and successfully construct EV battery recycling facilities and laboratories in South Africa, South Korea, Indonesia, etc., with its partners.</s><s coords="18,377.64,278.45,64.82,10.08;18,55.32,291.17,341.56,10.08;18,55.32,336.34,181.39,10.10;18,55.32,348.38,175.96,10.08;18,55.32,360.38,46.34,10.08">It is expected to deploy a recycling business in Europe in 2022 to accelerate its global business layout GEM has reached recycling cooperation with more than 500 OEMs and battery suppliers worldwide:</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="18,94.39,316.52,113.74,11.06">Stable resource channels</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="19,642.10,210.05,33.01,11.04">+61.6%</head><p><s coords="19,35.95,195.14,29.63,10.08;19,552.65,194.54,62.69,10.68;19,288.82,195.14,29.63,10.08;19,772.34,240.55,122.50,10.08;19,772.34,252.55,94.98,10.08;19,772.34,264.55,107.96,10.08;19,772.34,276.55,119.18,10.08;19,772.34,288.53,114.68,10.10;19,772.34,300.58,119.47,10.08;19,772.34,312.58,72.67,10.08">Tonnes Thousand USD 1 Tonnes In 2021, the YOY growth of EV battery comprehensive utilization business ranked first in GEM's comprehensive utilization sector, exceeding the growth rate of 54.83% of the total revenue</s></p><p><s coords="19,540.24,403.46,360.52,11.04;19,553.68,416.66,107.58,11.04">• GEM continues to make technological breakthroughs to improve the recycling capacity of EV batteries.</s><s coords="19,663.54,416.66,233.61,11.04;19,553.68,429.84,197.85,11.06">In 2025, the company's recycling target will be more than 20 times the recycling capacity in 2021.</s><s coords="19,754.24,429.84,136.53,11.06;19,553.68,443.09,347.19,11.04;19,553.68,456.29,318.98,11.04">With the advent of the battery retirement tide, GEM's EV battery recycling and reuse business is projected to become one of the main contributors to the company's future revenue.</s></p><p><s coords="19,45.60,401.93,441.43,11.06;19,59.06,415.18,432.44,11.04">• GEM's EV battery recycling and reuse business has shown substantial development momentum, expecting to recycle 30,000 tonnes of EV batteries and reuse around 2Gwh EoL batteries in 2022.</s><s coords="19,45.60,431.26,446.73,11.04;19,59.06,444.46,420.63,11.04;19,59.06,457.64,442.55,11.06">• It has been announced that GEM has had a total dismantling, processing and recycling capacity of end-of-life is 215,000 tonnes/year, the total planned capacity in the future for dismantling and recycling is close to 700,000 tonnes/year, and the total planned capacity for reuse exceeds 11GWh.</s><s coords="24,36.91,73.64,832.68,13.94;24,36.91,90.48,565.76,13.92;24,36.91,33.84,427.77,24.02;24,95.57,137.45,766.73,13.94">The industrial layout of "One core and Two extensions" of Brunp Recycling helps to form the internal regeneration and circulation of crucial battery materials within the value chain, resulting in the promotion of the sustainable development of CATL Battery Manufacturers Recycling: CATL (2/2) Relying on the Brunp Recycling, forging a one-stop recycling industry for the reuse, recycling and remanufacturing of the EV batteries</s></p><p><s coords="24,45.89,411.02,866.71,11.04;24,59.33,424.22,404.32,11.04">• According to the company's statistics, in the first quarter of 2022, a total of 21,300 tonnes of end-of-life batteries have been recycled and used to produce 18,000 tonnes of battery precursors, and the advantages of the internal circulation system will gradually create a marked effect.</s></p><p><s coords="24,45.89,443.41,856.19,11.06;24,59.33,456.65,200.44,11.04">• The establishment of Brunp integrated industrial park is conducive to further improve the CATL's strategic plan in new energy industry, giving full play to the advantages of industrial synergy and ensuring the supply of battery materials.</s><s coords="24,261.78,456.65,643.63,11.04">It's estimated that after 2035, CATL will be able to meet a significant part of the demand for raw materials by recycling retired battery materials.</s><s coords="25,36.91,73.64,509.78,13.94">The industrial alliance model could be an ideal business model and is led mainly by OEMs.</s><s coords="25,550.11,73.64,338.74,13.94;25,36.91,90.48,875.54,13.92;25,36.91,107.28,193.67,13.92">By leveraging the distribution service network and recycling technology of the member enterprises in the industrial chain, the recycling alliance can achieve a cost-effective and scalable recycling business and reduce vicious competition in the market.</s><s coords="25,234.26,107.28,679.70,13.92;25,36.91,33.84,541.88,24.02">However, this model is still in the initial trial stage of commercial operation, given that various stakeholders are involved Business Model: OEM-led Industrial Alliance as Recycler</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="25,150.12,137.88,237.84,13.92">Illustration of industrial alliance recycling</head><p><s coords="25,641.57,137.88,138.91,13.92">Business model analysis</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="25,537.24,189.38,37.47,13.92;25,532.20,207.17,47.31,13.92">Model features</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="25,543.24,278.98,25.25,13.94">Pros</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="25,542.04,351.02,27.88,13.92">Cons</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="25,545.64,413.30,20.75,13.92;25,535.32,431.05,41.09,13.94">Key players</head><p><s coords="25,614.21,173.52,278.55,10.08;25,614.21,185.52,165.50,10.08">The industrial chain's upstream and downstream alliance members are the primary recycler of EV batteries.</s><s coords="25,781.54,185.52,115.09,10.08;25,614.21,197.52,251.66,10.08;25,614.21,209.52,248.89,10.08;25,614.21,221.50,46.44,10.10">The alliance is the inevitable consequence of the Extended Producer Responsibility and the industrial collaborative cooperation mode driven by recycling economics.</s><s coords="25,662.41,221.50,231.78,10.10;25,614.21,233.54,250.98,10.08">OEMs often adopt this mode to build a recycling network through alliances to form a closed loop of the industrial chain.</s></p><p><s coords="25,614.21,256.56,247.25,10.08">Extensive recycling channels and strong technical expertise.</s><s coords="25,863.64,256.56,34.31,10.08;25,614.21,268.58,288.07,10.08;25,614.21,280.58,274.80,10.08;25,614.21,292.58,278.93,10.08;25,614.21,304.58,192.86,10.08">Through industrial collaboration, the vicious competition in the market, the cost of vehicle production, battery manufacturing and material recycling has been effectively reduced, and the overall recycling efficiency and mode operation efficiency have been improved</s></p><p><s coords="25,614.21,333.79,246.03,10.08">The negative impact of risk sharing is evident in this model.</s><s coords="25,862.44,333.79,39.67,10.08;25,614.21,345.79,215.02,10.08">Members are bound by each other through industrial alliances.</s><s coords="25,830.77,345.79,68.58,10.08;25,614.21,357.79,286.12,10.08;25,614.21,369.79,158.41,10.08">Enterprises need to bear the potential risks that other members of the battery recycling chain may bring, like uneven expertise.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="25,77.28,295.40,35.81,12.02;25,58.56,310.56,72.88,12.00">Vehicle manufacturers</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="25,242.47,205.64,36.40,12.02;25,224.23,220.80,72.88,12.00">Battery manufacturers</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="25,399.41,288.46,58.73,12.00;25,414.05,303.58,29.77,12.00;25,400.85,318.92,55.89,12.02">Recycle and Reuse enterprises</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="25,69.60,431.81,51.72,12.02">Customers</head><p><s coords="25,223.44,424.18,94.20,12.02;25,243.12,439.34,54.58,12.00;25,150.53,442.92,49.90,12.00;25,150.53,457.32,39.23,12.00">Vehicle dismantling enterprises End-of-life Vehicles</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="28,50.98,141.43,158.37,11.04">Difficulties in channel construction</head><p><s coords="28,50.98,154.39,245.51,10.08;28,50.98,166.39,163.47,10.08">Establishing a stable recycling channel is one of the recycling companies' most crucial success factors.</s><s coords="28,216.45,166.39,75.34,10.08;28,50.98,178.42,264.31,10.08;28,50.98,190.42,261.93,10.08;28,50.98,202.42,243.37,10.08">The establishment problem of the recycling channel significantly exposed due to the asymmetric information between the upstream enterprises with battery resources and the downstream recycling companies</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="28,50.98,220.66,114.74,11.04">Recycling cost challenges</head><p><s coords="28,50.98,233.64,239.04,10.08;28,50.98,245.64,259.78,10.08;28,50.98,257.64,269.79,10.08;28,50.98,269.64,111.59,10.08">At present, pricing mechanisms for the recycled end-of-life batteries are lacking, and the poor transparency causes the new batteries materials purchasing prices to drop away from the resale prices of recycled materials</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="28,200.50,341.09,76.34,10.56">Lack of standards</head><p><s coords="28,200.50,353.69,251.18,10.08;28,200.50,365.67,182.24,10.10">Types of power batteries are varied, from battery materials to internal structures and assembly techniques.</s><s coords="28,384.49,365.67,74.61,10.10;28,200.50,377.71,275.87,10.08">The lack of unified standards poses challenges to the evaluation of end-of-life batteries</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="28,200.50,395.59,88.80,10.56">Data source barriers</head><p><s coords="28,200.50,408.19,266.19,10.08;28,200.50,420.17,237.95,10.10;28,200.50,432.22,274.81,10.08;28,200.50,444.22,149.93,10.08">Third-party recyclers are challenging to obtain the data of end-oflife batteries from vehicle or battery manufacturers, which increases the difficulty of battery state estimation, remaining useful life prediction and safety assessment</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="28,374.14,141.31,176.48,10.56">High cost of reintegration and utilization</head><p><s coords="28,374.14,153.91,283.74,10.08;28,374.14,165.91,284.44,10.08">Only after disassembly, screening, re-integration, and other processes can the end-of-life batteries that meet the standard be put into reuse.</s></p><p><s coords="28,374.14,177.89,284.87,10.10;28,374.14,189.94,179.95,10.08">In addition, a series of costs such as battery management and logistics transportation lead to limited profit margins</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="28,374.14,207.82,247.19,10.56">Uncertain downstream demand due to security concerns</head><p><s coords="28,374.14,220.42,286.03,10.08;28,374.14,232.44,256.70,10.08;28,374.14,244.44,278.37,10.08">Subjected to the application scenarios and the application enterprise's concern about the potential safety hazard of secondary battery utilization, the reuse of end-of-life batteries is weaker than expected</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="28,550.66,341.09,175.06,10.56">Technical challenges of battery diversity</head><p><s coords="28,550.66,353.69,276.09,10.08;28,550.66,365.67,141.74,10.10">The disassembly and recovery technology process directly affect the recovery rate of high-value metals.</s><s coords="28,694.16,365.67,135.80,10.10;28,550.66,377.71,107.30,10.08">The diversity of batteries will also bring technical difficulties.</s><s coords="28,659.50,377.71,169.74,10.08;28,550.66,389.71,284.59,10.08">Moreover, the company needs to address the energy consumption and the environmental impact of the process</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="28,550.66,407.59,241.86,10.56">Difficulty to scale up due to unstable recycling channels</head><p><s coords="28,550.66,420.17,268.46,10.10;28,550.66,432.22,287.31,10.08;28,550.66,444.22,177.44,10.08">The massive investment in capacity construction in the early stage requires the companies to reach a specific scale of recycling end-of-life batteries to avoid significant profit pressure</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="28,725.76,141.31,148.43,10.56">Price uncertainty of raw materials</head><p><s coords="28,725.76,153.91,180.59,10.08;28,725.76,165.91,178.64,10.08;28,725.76,177.89,177.84,10.10;28,725.76,189.94,109.72,10.08">The price of recycled materials is affected by the double influence of the cost of recycling end-of-life batteries and the cost generated from the recycling process.</s><s coords="28,837.49,189.94,53.50,10.08;28,725.76,201.94,187.38,10.08;28,725.76,213.94,180.33,10.08;28,725.76,225.92,171.78,10.10;28,725.76,237.96,177.90,10.08;28,725.76,249.96,132.23,10.08">The frequent fluctuation of the price of metal raw materials will also affect the attractiveness of recycled materials, and the uncertainty of the price poses severe challenges to the downstream application of recycled materials</s></p><p><s coords="29,36.91,73.64,827.75,13.94;29,36.91,33.84,811.15,24.02">As the upstream industry, the technology and market trend of lithium battery and NEV industry are closely interrelated to the EV battery recycling Impact of upstream lithium battery and NEV industry trends on EV battery recycling</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="29,48.84,186.82,88.51,11.04;29,71.88,200.74,42.78,11.04">Rising prices of raw materials</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="29,52.92,264.00,80.18,11.04;29,52.68,277.92,81.00,11.04">Rapid iteration of battery chemistry</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="29,51.48,327.17,83.36,11.04;29,55.56,341.09,75.29,11.04;29,59.40,354.99,67.56,11.06;29,67.56,369.19,50.99,11.04">Upgrading battery pack and vehicle manufacturing technology</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="29,47.88,411.55,90.37,11.04;29,43.56,425.47,99.30,11.04;29,64.44,439.39,57.46,11.04">Accelerated battery service and ecological construction</head><p><s coords="29,174.00,182.33,332.68,10.08;29,188.18,194.33,326.87,10.08;29,188.18,206.33,279.38,10.08">• The productivity growth of upstream metal resource exploitation is lower than that of downstream application industries, and the mismatch between resource supply and demand is significant, leading to metal price fluctuations</s></p><p><s coords="29,174.00,245.02,3.53,9.46;29,196.58,244.80,274.13,10.08;29,196.58,256.80,295.55,10.08;29,196.58,268.78,265.70,10.10">• High nickelization and low cobalt of ternary batteries and Li-battery alternatives, which correspondingly reduce the dependence on precious elements through material innovation, are global R&amp;D hot topics.</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="29,174.00,281.04,3.53,9.46">•</head><p><s coords="29,196.58,280.82,300.05,10.08;29,196.58,292.82,46.63,10.08">The installation of LFP battery increases rapidly due to its cost and safety advantages</s></p><p><s coords="29,174.00,322.01,338.25,10.10;29,188.18,334.06,314.64,10.08;29,188.18,346.06,170.28,10.08;29,174.00,358.06,305.63,10.08;29,188.18,370.06,171.85,10.08">• Battery pack technologies such as module-free design (CTP) and battery chassis integration technology (CTC) improve space utilization and mileage range and achieve high efficiency and cost reduction • Groundswell of the opinion of EV and battery pack standardization, but standardization itself is proceeding slowly.</s></p><p><s coords="29,174.00,411.29,338.71,10.08;29,188.18,423.29,293.29,10.08;29,188.18,435.27,151.13,10.10">• Battery Bank (BaaS) and other on-demand battery replacement service provide centralized full life-cycle operation management such as battery leasing, charging, maintenance and swapping</s></p><p><s coords="29,571.01,182.33,324.03,10.08;29,585.17,194.33,315.18,10.08;29,585.17,206.33,250.07,10.08">• The critical metals in battery manufacturing can be recycled from end-of-life batteries, effectively supplement the shortage of resources, and promote the development of the recycling industry from the demand side</s></p><p><s coords="29,571.01,244.80,341.55,10.08;29,585.17,256.80,206.43,10.08;29,571.01,268.78,340.83,10.10;29,585.17,280.82,320.85,10.08;29,585.17,292.82,142.40,10.08">• The fast innovation of battery technology and the diversity of specifications raise the difficulty of battery disassembly and recycling • The cost reduction trend of batteries may bring challenges to the profitability of the recycling industry, promote recycling companies to develop more efficient recycling technologies and models</s></p><p><s coords="29,571.01,322.01,311.79,10.10;29,585.17,334.06,227.80,10.08">• Highly integrated and structural batteries have increased the difficulty of battery disassembly and technical barriers to recovery.</s><s coords="29,814.66,334.06,92.66,10.08;29,585.17,346.06,263.49,10.08;29,571.01,358.06,320.48,10.08;29,585.17,370.06,328.54,10.08">The vehicle companies and their partners will take on greater responsibility for recycling • The standardization of battery packs will benefit the automatic disassembly process of batteries, promoting the standardization process of battery recycling</s></p><p><s coords="29,571.01,399.29,321.04,10.08;29,585.17,411.29,155.05,10.08;29,571.01,423.29,341.43,10.08;29,585.17,435.27,308.29,10.10;29,585.17,447.31,299.77,10.08">• The rise of battery services has led to a more centralized recycling channel, making it easy to create a scale effect • Battery banks, charging stations are conducive to strengthening the information traceability and management of the battery life cycle, accurately predicting battery retirement, improving the battery recycling efficiency and values</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="29,129.53,135.19,301.29,12.00;29,644.88,135.19,195.07,12.00">Related Trends of the EV battery recycling upstream industry Impact on EV battery recycling industry</head><p><s coords="29,36.50,488.12,143.57,7.92">Source: public information, Deloitte analysis</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="30,36.91,33.84,527.04,24.02">Business Implications for Battery Recycling Companies</head><p><s coords="30,36.91,73.64,630.13,13.94">Leading battery recycling companies should carefully consider the following issues from a strategic perspective:</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="30,50.54,184.68,93.61,13.92;30,72.38,201.48,50.06,13.92">Overall strategic planning</head><p><s coords="30,54.38,217.44,86.03,12.60">(Where to play)</s></p><p><s coords="30,172.68,163.80,354.53,12.00">• Which sectors of the recycling business should the company invest in?</s><s coords="30,530.04,163.80,245.87,12.00">Does the main business involve reuse or recycling?</s></p><p><s coords="30,172.68,181.06,257.20,12.02">• What business model should the company adopt?</s><s coords="30,432.71,181.06,296.06,12.02">What are the core advantages and key points to profitability?</s></p><p><s coords="30,172.68,198.62,650.76,12.00">• Does the company consider the extension or closed-loop construction along the up and downstream, or specialization in recycling?</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="30,63.98,355.92,66.97,13.94;30,46.46,373.73,102.02,13.92;30,45.98,391.73,102.78,13.92;30,64.94,408.99,64.89,12.02">Capabilities development and Industrial synergy (How to win)</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="30,172.39,276.60,130.47,12.02">Capabilities development:</head><p><s coords="30,172.39,293.93,671.39,12.00">• Channels -How to construct and distribute self-owned recycling networks to ensure adequate resources and stable recycling channels?</s><s coords="30,846.61,293.93,40.72,12.00;30,186.55,308.33,296.52,12.00">Through M&amp;A integration, strategic alliance or exchange agreements?</s><s coords="30,172.39,325.83,280.98,12.02">• Technology -Which recycling process route to choose?</s><s coords="30,456.45,325.83,403.12,12.02;30,186.55,340.27,57.14,12.00">How to improve the recovery rate and reduce recycling costs through technological innovation?</s><s coords="30,172.39,357.55,515.34,12.00">• Capacity -How to plan on recycling capacity improvement in the next 3-5 years to achieve scale effect?</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="30,172.39,383.93,92.02,12.02">Industrial synergy:</head><p><s coords="30,172.39,401.50,639.89,12.00">• Upstream -How to react to the rapid technological change and market trends in the upstream lithium battery and NEV industry?</s><s coords="30,814.88,401.50,87.01,12.00;30,186.55,415.90,344.24,12.00">How to cooperate with battery manufacturers and OEMs who enjoy channel advantages?</s><s coords="30,172.39,433.16,724.87,12.02;30,186.55,447.60,151.15,12.00">• Downstream -Does the company need to extend to the reuse, regenerating or remanufacturing and develop the capacity of battery raw materials production such as precursors?</s><s coords="30,340.77,447.60,433.86,12.00">How to compete with metal raw material suppliers such as Li-salt production companies?</s></p><p><s coords="31,36.91,33.84,552.15,24.02">Business Implications for Lithium and Battery Companies</s></p><p><s coords="31,36.91,73.64,731.82,13.94">Leading lithium companies and battery manufacturers should carefully consider the following issues from a strategic perspective:</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="31,50.54,184.68,93.61,13.92;31,72.38,201.48,50.06,13.92">Overall strategic planning</head><p><s coords="31,54.38,217.44,86.03,12.60">(Where to play)</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="31,63.98,355.92,66.97,13.94;31,46.46,373.73,102.02,13.92;31,45.98,391.73,102.78,13.92;31,64.94,408.99,64.89,12.02">Capabilities development and Industrial synergy (How to win)</head><p><s coords="31,172.68,142.49,319.32,12.02">• Does the company consider expanding into recycling business?</s><s coords="31,494.82,142.49,398.77,12.02">Based on what background, should the company get involved in battery recycling?</s></p><p><s coords="31,186.84,156.94,177.23,12.00">What is the core business objective?</s><s coords="31,172.68,174.22,460.56,12.00">• If entering the recycling field, which industry sectors should the company plan to engage in?</s><s coords="31,636.07,174.22,255.89,12.00;31,186.84,188.60,85.19,12.02">How can the company take advantage of the original battery business?</s><s coords="31,172.68,206.16,257.18,12.00">• What business model should the company adopt?</s><s coords="31,432.70,206.16,424.92,12.00;31,186.84,220.56,216.60,12.00">Is it to do independent recycling capability R&amp;D or seek industrial collaborations up and downstream based on the original business?</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="31,172.39,283.85,130.39,12.00">Capabilities development:</head><p><s coords="31,172.39,301.13,726.24,12.00;31,186.55,315.53,79.93,12.00">• Channel -How does the company leverage its sales network to build a reverse logistics recycling channel and form a closed-loop utilization of endof-life batteries?</s><s coords="31,172.39,333.07,585.11,12.00">• Technology -How to make use of existing battery manufacturing technology for recycling technology transformation?</s><s coords="31,760.34,333.07,99.62,12.00;31,186.55,347.47,455.10,12.00">Independent R&amp;D of innovative recycling technology or technique patent purchase to improve recycling efficiency?</s><s coords="31,172.39,364.75,695.46,12.00">• Capacity -How to plan on recycling capacity improvement in the next 3-5 years, and realize industrialization to support its original business?</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="31,172.39,391.18,91.99,12.00">Industrial synergy:</head><p><s coords="31,172.39,408.70,730.29,12.00">• Upstream -How does the company supplement resources through recycling to mitigate the bargaining power against upstream resource suppliers?</s></p><p><s coords="31,172.39,425.98,574.59,12.00">• Downstream -Should the company rely on supply or establish cooperative relationships with recycling enterprises?</s><s coords="31,749.81,425.98,124.72,12.00;31,186.55,440.40,324.58,12.00">Or vertically integrate the recycling enterprises with technological advantages through M&amp;A?</s><s coords="31,513.73,440.40,393.15,12.00">How to cooperate with OEMs in recycling closed-loop supply chain construction?</s></p><p><s coords="32,36.91,33.84,423.88,24.02">Business Implications for Automotive OEMs</s></p><p><s coords="32,36.91,73.64,573.29,13.94">Leading automotive OEMs should carefully consider the following issues from a strategic perspective:</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="32,50.54,184.68,93.61,13.92;32,72.38,201.48,50.06,13.92">Overall strategic planning</head><p><s coords="32,54.38,217.44,86.03,12.60">(Where to play)</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="32,63.98,355.92,66.97,13.94;32,46.46,373.73,102.02,13.92;32,45.98,391.73,102.78,13.92;32,64.94,408.99,64.89,12.02">Capabilities development and Industrial synergy (How to win)</head><p><s coords="32,172.68,150.00,4.20,11.26;32,192.60,149.74,673.84,12.00">• Based on the company's strategic consideration and its capability's current situation, should the company get involved in battery recycling?</s></p><p><s coords="32,172.68,167.28,4.20,11.26;32,192.60,167.02,308.23,12.00">• If entering the recycling field, does it involve reuse or recycling?</s><s coords="32,503.90,167.02,362.14,12.00;32,192.60,181.42,121.16,12.00">How can the company take advantage of the technology of the original car manufacturing business?</s><s coords="32,172.68,199.22,4.20,11.26;32,192.60,198.96,303.94,12.00">• Which industry sectors should the company plan to engage in?</s><s coords="32,499.37,198.96,177.23,12.00">What is the core business objective?</s><s coords="32,679.22,198.96,205.83,12.00;32,192.60,213.36,435.59,12.00">Is it to do independent recycling capability R&amp;D or seek industrial collaborations up and downstream based on the original business?</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="32,172.39,269.40,130.47,12.02">Capabilities development:</head><p><s coords="32,172.39,286.99,4.20,11.26;32,194.95,286.73,696.01,12.00;32,194.95,301.13,384.31,12.00">• Channel -How to improve the utilization of the existing sales network and establish a recycling channel for retired batteries with stable sources and guaranteed quality to avoid losing resources to other third-party channels?</s><s coords="32,172.39,318.91,4.20,11.26;32,194.95,318.65,700.24,12.00;32,194.95,333.07,361.52,12.00">• Technology -Assess the current status of its own capabilities, including gaps in battery recycling technology capabilities, and its supply of retired batteries, and determine the depth of its involvement in battery recycling?</s><s coords="32,172.39,350.61,4.20,11.26;32,194.95,350.35,683.57,12.00;32,194.95,364.75,105.82,12.00">• Economic -Based on the cost-effectiveness of possible business models, further decide how to achieve technical capacity building: self-R&amp;D, partnership, or M&amp;A?</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="32,172.39,391.18,91.99,12.00">Industrial synergy:</head><p><s coords="32,172.39,408.96,4.20,11.26;32,194.95,408.70,580.48,12.00">• Upstream -Is it possible that the supply constraints of upstream materials be alleviated through the recycling business?</s><s coords="32,778.26,408.70,103.82,12.00;32,194.95,423.10,502.80,12.00">Whether and how do OEMs seek cooperation with upstream battery and material companies to obtain technical capabilities?</s><s coords="32,172.39,440.66,4.20,11.26;32,194.95,440.40,609.55,12.00">• Downstream -How do OEMs cooperate with downstream recycling companies to supplement the battery recycling network?</s><s coords="32,807.10,440.40,72.95,12.00;32,194.95,454.80,621.72,12.00">Is it possible to cooperate with energy and power suppliers to expand the reuse scenario when the technology and business model are mature?</s></p></div><figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_0" coords="9,559.85,276.48,127.03,10.08;9,559.85,288.46,98.71,10.10;9,559.85,300.50,88.76,10.08;9,77.76,324.70,386.90,11.59;9,77.76,339.58,379.24,11.59;9,91.20,352.11,356.35,11.06;9,77.76,366.24,389.61,11.59;9,91.20,378.79,117.55,11.04;9,708.38,276.74,43.74,10.08;9,714.65,288.72,31.13,10.10;9,511.34,405.26,398.72,11.04;9,524.78,417.26,219.81,11.04;9,511.34,432.14,392.37,11.04;9,524.78,443.90,272.30,11.04;9,511.34,458.81,384.21,11.04;9,895.68,464.09,3.65,7.20;9,524.78,470.57,125.71,11.04;9,511.34,324.46,376.12,11.62;9,511.34,339.39,84.33,11.59"><head>＋</head><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="9,91.20,325.25,373.46,11.04;9,77.76,339.58,379.24,11.59;9,91.20,352.11,356.35,11.06;9,77.76,366.24,389.61,11.59;9,91.20,378.79,117.55,11.04;9,708.38,276.74,43.74,10.08;9,714.65,288.72,31.13,10.10;9,511.34,405.26,398.72,11.04;9,524.78,417.26,219.81,11.04;9,511.34,432.14,392.37,11.04;9,524.78,443.90,272.30,11.04;9,511.34,458.81,384.21,11.04;9,895.68,464.09,3.65,7.20;9,524.78,470.57,125.71,11.04;9,511.34,324.46,376.12,11.62;9,511.34,339.39,84.33,11.59">Increase value: optimize the utilization of batteries and maximize the residual value ＋ Cost reduction: reduce the cost of energy storage, low-speed electric vehicles and other related industries, and promote the development of the circular economy ＋ Reduce pollution: effectively reduce the pollution of waste lithium-ion batteries and reduce waste of resources End-of-life battery -Cost issues: The pyro has a large investment and high energy consumption in the early stage, while the hydro is relative time-consuming -Environmental pollution: Both pyro and hydro cause severe environmental pollution easily, and the requirements for pollution treatment are high -Uncertainty: Emerging techniques such as biological processes and supercritical CO 2 extraction are still in startup ＋ High recovery rate: Mature in technology, thus the resource recovery rate is high ＋ Simple process:</s></p></div></figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_1" coords="12,530.13,90.48,89.07,13.92;12,619.78,97.26,4.75,9.36;12,627.94,90.48,278.36,13.92;12,36.91,107.28,611.88,13.92;12,36.91,33.84,647.88,24.02;12,313.34,161.23,96.77,13.92;12,84.10,202.20,37.63,12.00;12,67.30,217.34,70.96,12.00;12,36.48,486.85,271.14,7.92;12,65.35,428.28,75.59,12.00;12,74.98,443.40,56.12,12.00;12,73.58,266.16,88.16,10.10;12,78.55,305.95,71.40,10.08;12,74.26,344.21,79.84,10.08;12,72.55,382.15,83.12,10.08;12,300.58,263.40,132.11,11.06;12,235.54,304.18,261.82,11.06;12,244.18,338.11,244.83,11.04;12,275.14,352.03,182.72,11.04;12,232.90,381.86,267.35,11.04;12,594.14,336.55,292.18,11.04;12,682.97,350.45,114.50,11.06;12,578.54,298.70,323.31,11.04;12,669.77,312.62,141.06,11.04;12,655.37,264.89,169.91,11.06;12,616.01,381.02,248.39,11.04;12,694.49,161.23,88.85,13.92;13,36.91,73.64,885.89,13.94;13,36.91,90.48,870.05,13.92;13,36.91,107.28,149.29,13.92;13,36.91,33.84,670.61,24.02;13,464.93,171.53,48.05,10.68;13,92.54,136.85,310.47,13.92;13,513.53,136.85,350.98,13.92;13,864.72,135.95,4.75,9.36"><head/><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="12,530.13,90.48,89.07,13.92;12,619.78,97.26,4.75,9.36;12,627.94,90.48,278.36,13.92;12,36.91,107.28,611.88,13.92;12,36.91,33.84,647.88,24.02;12,313.34,161.23,96.77,13.92;12,84.10,202.20,37.63,12.00;12,67.30,217.34,70.96,12.00;12,36.48,486.85,271.14,7.92;12,319.03,304.18,178.33,11.06;12,244.18,338.11,244.83,11.04;12,275.14,352.03,182.72,11.04;12,232.90,381.86,267.35,11.04;12,594.14,336.55,292.18,11.04;12,682.97,350.45,114.50,11.06;12,578.54,298.70,323.31,11.04;12,669.77,312.62,141.06,11.04;12,655.37,264.89,169.91,11.06;12,616.01,381.02,248.39,11.04;12,694.49,161.23,88.85,13.92;13,36.91,73.64,885.89,13.94">supercritical CO 2 extraction, are still in the early stages of research and development; currently, in China, EV battery recycling enterprises' processes are mainly based on hydro Recycle: Mainstream Battery-grade Material Extraction Techniques Hydrometallurgy Process characteristics Source: Anson Securities, Dongguan Securities, public information, Deloitte analysis purity, but relatively long recycle period Relatively more complicated, and needs to be adjusted optimized for certain battery chemistries Require process effluent treatment to avoid water pollution Simpler pretreatment methods but not effective for Lithium-ironphosphate (LFP) batteries The recovery rate is relatively lower, but is capable of recovering various heavy metals such as Hg and Zn High investment and energy-intensive Require gas clean-up process to avoid toxic air emission Pyrometallurgy The distinctions in battery chemical structure and properties determine the recycling mode, reuse method, value and market size of end-of-life EV batteries.</s><s coords="13,36.91,90.48,870.05,13.92;13,36.91,107.28,149.29,13.92;13,36.91,33.84,670.61,24.02;13,464.93,171.53,48.05,10.68;13,92.54,136.85,310.47,13.92;13,513.53,136.85,350.98,13.92;13,864.72,135.95,4.75,9.36">The development of reuse of LFP is restricted to the current conditions, and the future recycling market is expected to be dominated by the direct recycle of ternary (NMC) batteries Recycle: Prospects of Battery Recycling in Different Chemical Systems Billion USD 2 Comparison of batteries in different chemical systems Projection on the China recycling market size by battery type 1</s></p></div></figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_2" coords="15,124.80,137.11,345.09,13.92;15,36.91,73.64,870.62,13.94;15,36.91,90.48,850.05,13.92;15,36.91,107.28,268.79,13.92;15,36.91,33.84,562.78,24.02;15,67.32,414.19,82.80,9.12;15,67.32,435.82,93.27,9.12;15,67.32,455.50,83.67,9.12;15,67.32,466.30,73.14,9.12;15,665.18,152.26,233.49,13.92;15,665.18,169.04,95.63,13.94;15,665.18,191.40,201.63,12.00;15,678.62,205.56,197.94,11.04;15,678.62,218.76,189.43,11.04;15,678.62,231.94,215.29,11.06;15,678.62,245.18,199.71,11.04"><head/><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="15,124.80,137.11,345.09,13.92;15,36.91,73.64,870.62,13.94;15,36.91,90.48,850.05,13.92;15,36.91,107.28,268.79,13.92;15,36.91,33.84,562.78,24.02;15,67.32,414.19,82.80,9.12;15,67.32,435.82,93.27,9.12;15,67.32,455.50,83.67,9.12;15,67.32,466.30,73.14,9.12;15,665.18,152.26,233.49,13.92;15,665.18,169.04,95.63,13.94;15,665.18,191.40,201.63,12.00;15,678.62,205.56,197.94,11.04;15,678.62,218.76,189.43,11.04;15,678.62,231.94,215.29,11.06;15,678.62,245.18,199.71,11.04">Lithium battery industrial chain extends to battery recyclingWith the transformation of the industry to market-driven development, the lithium battery and NEV industry will further evolve from a chained-form to a mesh ecology with deeper cooperation and mutual empowerment, in which each sector of the industry chain shows the trend of extending to battery recycling in various forms and different degrees Development Trend of Li-battery and NEV Industrial Chain Industrial Chain Sector Industrial Chain Direction Industrial Chain Future Expansion Direction Enterprises in multiple sectors extend to battery recycling • Technology-based extension: Resource refining enterprises and anode, cathode raw material manufacturers have the technical similarity in recycling and extraction technology, which drives their extension to the recycling.</s></p></div></figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_3" coords="15,36.48,486.85,143.57,7.92;15,251.86,344.52,100.99,10.10;15,355.85,213.29,76.16,10.08;15,347.21,226.01,93.41,10.08;16,48.56,307.79,7.92,36.25;16,48.56,280.10,7.92,25.54;16,44.00,381.98,7.92,23.74;16,51.68,372.48,7.92,42.14;16,43.84,434.79,17.52,28.17;16,36.91,73.64,873.31,13.94;16,36.91,90.48,839.47,13.92;16,36.91,107.28,619.10,13.92;16,36.91,33.84,354.95,24.02;16,690.72,266.52,20.14,10.08;16,708.34,322.56,103.50,10.08;16,771.50,345.48,79.77,10.10;16,604.66,293.28,191.99,10.08;16,533.57,432.29,16.51,10.08;16,78.31,271.60,70.38,7.92;16,82.63,281.20,62.21,7.92;16,100.39,290.80,26.37,7.92;16,80.95,371.48,65.32,7.92;16,76.87,381.11,73.43,7.92;16,85.27,390.71,56.53,7.92;16,78.55,400.31,70.14,7.92;16,76.39,409.91,74.34,7.92;16,78.07,426.25,71.04,7.92;16,79.03,435.85,69.28,7.92;16,83.11,445.45,61.01,7.92;16,89.59,455.05,48.07,7.92;16,99.67,464.68,27.77,7.92;16,384.34,137.52,76.72,10.08;16,491.95,137.52,89.19,10.08;16,629.26,137.52,25.44,10.08;16,739.20,137.52,31.68,10.08;16,831.14,137.52,72.16,10.08;16,267.91,137.31,94.25,10.10;16,159.05,137.45,94.45,10.08;16,42.10,231.27,16.76,11.06;16,33.94,245.23,32.94,11.04;16,80.83,232.13,65.53,10.08;16,95.47,244.83,36.42,10.10;16,79.51,321.54,68.27,7.92;16,79.27,331.14,68.67,7.92;16,80.71,340.74,65.97,7.92;16,105.67,350.32,16.18,7.94;16,498.19,241.71,74.61,10.10;16,205.75,379.18,20.09,10.10;16,670.56,378.86,65.68,10.08;16,417.05,379.44,20.07,10.08;16,603.79,396.12,79.95,10.08;16,629.23,408.82,29.01,10.10;16,204.79,400.75,22.89,10.08;16,36.50,488.12,204.48,7.92;16,239.59,192.97,39.93,7.92;16,333.77,192.97,59.33,7.92;16,455.78,192.97,32.23,7.92;16,554.30,192.97,61.39,7.92;16,665.04,192.97,66.41,7.92;16,780.60,192.97,61.62,7.92;16,251.57,457.95,24.55,10.10;16,604.58,458.35,24.53,10.08;16,667.46,458.28,35.22,10.08;17,36.91,33.84,369.21,24.02;17,36.91,73.64,876.14,13.94;17,36.91,90.48,220.73,13.92;17,170.06,137.88,198.37,13.92;17,78.62,221.69,23.94,12.00;17,413.21,214.06,35.44,12.00;17,395.45,229.16,70.67,12.02;17,240.07,306.70,89.82,11.04;17,241.54,320.60,86.79,11.06;17,246.82,334.56,76.36,11.04;17,66.38,418.70,51.71,12.00;17,238.25,410.64,94.18,12.00;17,257.93,425.76,54.58,12.00;17,74.33,328.03,12.00,34.54;17,74.33,274.47,12.00,50.44;17,159.72,433.85,49.92,12.00;17,165.00,448.23,39.28,12.02;17,204.26,210.50,98.75,12.00;17,641.57,137.88,138.91,13.92;17,36.50,488.12,332.95,7.92;17,537.24,189.38,37.47,13.92;17,532.20,207.17,47.31,13.92;17,543.24,269.50,25.22,13.92;17,542.04,340.70,27.88,13.92;17,545.64,402.96,20.78,13.94;17,535.32,420.77,41.08,13.92;17,614.21,176.74,255.84,10.08;17,614.21,191.16,181.12,10.08;17,814.77,191.16,28.99,10.08;17,614.21,205.56,246.57,10.08;17,614.21,219.96,234.54,10.08;17,614.21,259.20,285.15,10.10;17,614.21,271.25,271.98,10.08;17,614.21,329.47,287.70,10.08;17,614.21,341.47,266.44,10.08;17,614.21,353.47,129.59,10.08;17,392.78,408.07,78.44,10.56;17,392.78,434.98,97.94,10.58;18,36.91,73.64,880.17,13.94;18,36.91,90.48,731.33,13.92;18,36.91,33.84,394.09,24.02;18,251.38,137.19,454.87,13.94;18,44.47,170.62,869.50,10.08;18,44.47,182.60,725.92,10.10;18,562.13,217.75,291.59,12.00;18,547.06,367.42,27.32,11.04;18,612.62,418.85,27.32,11.04;18,748.78,349.54,121.42,10.08"><head/><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="16,82.98,73.64,708.83,13.94">battery recycling, which has a substantial development momentum, is taking shape to support a sustainable EV supply chain.</s><s coords="16,795.23,73.64,115.00,13.94;16,36.91,90.48,839.47,13.92;16,36.91,107.28,619.10,13.92;16,36.91,33.84,25.35,24.02;17,103.88,73.64,809.16,13.94;17,36.91,90.48,220.73,13.92;17,36.50,488.12,332.95,7.92;17,663.14,176.74,206.91,10.08;17,614.21,191.16,181.12,10.08;17,814.77,191.16,28.99,10.08;17,614.21,205.56,246.57,10.08;17,614.21,219.96,234.54,10.08;17,614.21,259.20,285.15,10.10;17,614.21,271.25,271.98,10.08;17,614.21,329.47,287.70,10.08;17,614.21,341.47,266.44,10.08;17,614.21,353.47,129.59,10.08;17,392.78,408.07,78.44,10.56;17,392.78,434.98,97.94,10.58;18,36.91,73.64,580.71,13.94">Up and downstream players in the industry use their advantages to develop vertical cooperation and seek opportunities to gradually extend the industry chain coverage, forming a closed-loop industrial chain from battery recycling to battery material reproduction and integration EV recycling companies, as the primary recycler of EV batteries, independently establish a recycling service network to complete the process from battery recycling to resource utilization Source: CITIC Securities, Everbright Securities, Tianfeng Securities, public information, Deloitte analysis recycling companies, as the primary recycler of EV batteries, generally are entrusted by battery vehicle manufacturers to complete the transportation, recycling and subsequent resource utilization of end-of-life EV batteries Highly mature and professional recycling processes, which are widely used, can realize more efficient recycling of end-of-life EV batteries The self-built recycling service network poses severe challenges on its high recycling costs, difficulties in transportation and storage, and limited material resale channels End-of-life battery Production/Sales chain GEM pays attention to the construction and maintenance of recycling networks and industrial ecology.</s><s coords="18,620.84,73.64,296.24,13.94;18,36.91,90.48,731.33,13.92;18,36.91,33.84,394.09,24.02;18,251.38,137.19,454.87,13.94;18,44.47,170.62,869.50,10.08;18,44.47,182.60,69.48,10.10">Meanwhile, the company is committed to building a new energy life-cycle value chain and has established an industrial chain advantage in the field of power battery green treatment Third-party Battery Recyclers: GEM (1/2) The pioneer circular enterprise of end-of-life battery comprehensive utilization GEM, incorporated in 2001, started with the recycling of nickel-cobalt resources and mobile phone batteries and has gradually expanded to the recycling of waste electrical, electronic equipment, end-of-life vehicles and EV batteries.</s><s coords="18,115.71,182.60,654.69,10.10">Over the past 20 years, GEM has been committed to the dual-track driven strategic development of "exploiting urban mines + developing new energy materials".</s><s coords="18,562.13,217.75,291.59,12.00">KSF 2: Globally-advanced new energy life-cycle value chain</s></p></div></figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_4" coords="18,167.04,378.46,71.11,10.08;18,299.98,316.80,123.24,11.04;18,273.53,376.36,10.10,19.92;18,271.85,410.10,13.13,19.92;18,273.53,443.80,10.11,19.94;18,320.57,379.40,121.79,10.10;18,320.57,442.01,99.89,10.08;18,322.73,452.81,111.50,10.08;18,320.57,401.11,102.51,10.08;18,320.57,411.94,131.93,10.08;18,320.57,422.74,52.07,10.08;18,268.10,336.34,178.60,10.10;18,268.10,348.38,170.74,10.08;18,268.10,360.38,114.01,10.08;18,614.09,315.70,182.50,11.04;18,36.50,488.12,284.81,7.92;18,506.93,341.91,52.24,10.10;18,506.93,352.75,34.90,10.08;18,632.78,441.43,49.19,10.08;18,632.78,452.23,74.94,10.08;19,36.91,73.64,859.68,13.94;19,36.91,90.48,872.68,13.92;19,36.91,107.28,144.35,13.92;19,36.91,33.84,394.09,24.02;19,138.29,137.88,278.12,13.92;19,603.14,137.86,245.87,13.92;19,60.94,336.89,24.80,11.04;19,134.06,284.35,24.80,11.04;19,207.22,222.29,24.80,11.04;19,135.50,372.10,22.16,11.04;19,62.35,372.10,22.16,11.04;19,208.66,372.10,22.16,11.04;19,131.35,253.44,30.13,11.04;19,590.06,278.11,30.32,11.04;19,697.34,231.79,30.32,11.04;19,594.12,372.10,22.16,11.04;19,701.40,372.10,22.16,11.04"><head/><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="18,322.73,452.81,111.50,10.08;18,320.57,401.11,102.51,10.08;18,320.57,411.94,131.93,10.08;18,320.57,422.74,52.07,10.08;18,268.10,336.34,178.60,10.10;18,268.10,348.38,170.74,10.08;18,268.10,360.38,114.01,10.08;18,614.09,315.70,182.50,11.04;18,36.50,488.12,284.81,7.92;18,506.93,341.91,52.24,10.10;18,506.93,352.75,34.90,10.08;18,632.78,441.43,49.19,10.08;18,632.78,452.23,74.94,10.08;19,36.91,73.64,506.15,13.94">and remanufacturing parks Other recycling networks covering more than 60% of total NEV in China Country-wide integrated recycling networks and the unique "2+N+2" pattern of power battery recycling businesses GEM Revenue share by business in 2021 Source: company website, company annual report, public information, Deloitte analysis Urban mines business New energy materials business GEM's battery recycling capacity and business income have rapidly grown in recent years.</s><s coords="19,546.48,73.64,350.11,13.94;19,36.91,90.48,136.43,13.92">The company has included "expanding recycling" as one of its development strategies.</s><s coords="19,177.49,90.48,732.10,13.92;19,36.91,107.28,144.35,13.92;19,36.91,33.84,394.09,24.02">With the advent of the battery retirement tide, GEM will further expand the comprehensive utilization scale of the company's EV battery in the near future Third-party Battery Recyclers: GEM (2/2)</s></p></div></figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_5" coords="19,317.42,339.77,14.00,11.06;19,390.58,284.09,13.99,11.04;19,463.70,222.29,13.99,11.04;19,313.30,372.10,22.16,11.04;19,386.45,372.10,22.16,11.04;19,459.58,372.10,22.16,11.04;19,382.27,259.16,30.15,11.06;19,105.05,175.25,79.22,12.00;19,360.38,175.37,72.01,12.00;19,553.01,174.84,211.73,12.00;19,36.50,489.97,284.81,7.92;19,36.50,499.57,330.34,7.92;20,36.91,73.64,861.59,13.94;20,36.91,90.48,573.42,13.92;20,36.91,33.84,420.99,24.02;20,86.69,137.19,784.55,13.94;20,44.47,170.62,855.17,10.08;20,44.47,182.60,845.52,10.10;20,102.79,217.75,298.01,12.00;20,42.53,251.28,142.71,10.10;20,55.97,263.33,134.08,10.08;20,55.97,275.33,122.59,10.08;20,55.97,287.33,124.98,10.08;20,55.97,299.31,123.53,10.10;20,55.97,311.35,142.68,10.08;20,55.97,323.35,88.96,10.08;20,42.53,338.47,154.58,10.08;20,55.97,350.47,127.76,10.08;20,55.97,362.50,131.38,10.08;20,55.97,374.50,134.17,10.08;20,55.97,386.50,107.01,10.08;20,55.97,398.50,136.68,10.08;20,55.97,410.48,127.19,10.10;20,55.97,422.52,138.76,10.08;20,55.97,434.52,134.97,10.08;20,55.97,446.52,129.85,10.08;20,240.74,257.64,179.82,10.56;20,500.62,251.52,399.23,10.08;20,500.62,263.50,394.36,10.10;20,500.62,275.54,348.11,10.08;20,519.62,313.56,162.58,10.08;20,510.26,325.68,181.78,10.68;20,539.02,217.75,337.44,12.00;20,733.70,326.30,152.86,9.12;20,733.70,337.13,136.44,9.12;20,733.70,347.93,138.66,9.12;20,733.70,358.73,159.08,9.12;20,733.70,369.53,59.20,9.12;20,522.98,371.67,12.11,10.10;20,534.98,376.35,3.42,6.74;20,540.50,371.67,37.09,10.10;20,529.94,384.43,40.89,10.08;20,536.23,345.98,28.06,16.10;20,630.70,371.67,52.78,10.10;20,636.70,384.43,40.89,10.08;20,642.91,345.98,28.06,16.10;20,522.29,440.78,13.53,10.08;20,535.73,445.46,3.08,6.72;20,541.01,440.78,37.07,10.08;20,529.97,453.49,40.89,10.10;20,536.23,416.37,28.06,16.10;20,629.93,440.78,11.61,10.08;20,641.45,445.46,3.08,6.72;20,646.73,440.78,37.09,10.08;20,636.65,453.49,40.89,10.10;20,642.91,416.37,28.06,16.10;20,517.56,295.34,167.63,10.08;20,745.08,294.43,136.86,10.08;20,768.50,310.10,91.50,10.08;20,733.90,408.07,154.51,9.12;20,733.90,418.87,139.85,9.12;20,733.90,429.67,151.11,9.12;20,733.90,440.45,156.87,9.14;20,733.90,451.30,79.14,9.12;20,762.48,391.92,104.14,10.08;20,237.14,421.61,69.59,9.14;20,237.14,438.77,196.49,9.14;20,36.50,489.97,284.81,7.92;20,36.50,499.57,253.12,7.92;21,36.91,73.64,854.11,13.94;21,36.91,90.48,291.41,13.92;21,36.91,33.84,420.99,24.02;21,45.82,445.85,858.69,10.08;21,59.26,457.85,800.53,10.08;21,544.18,174.86,21.35,10.56;21,583.49,174.86,51.19,10.56;21,667.85,174.86,37.53,10.56;21,753.98,174.86,27.46,10.56;21,809.40,174.86,83.50,10.56;21,542.50,201.24,24.70,10.10;21,599.09,201.24,20.24,10.10;21,659.93,201.24,53.31,10.10;21,742.70,201.24,50.40,10.10;21,839.88,201.24,22.65,10.10;21,542.50,225.38,24.73,10.08;21,599.09,225.38,20.23,10.08;21,658.25,225.38,57.01,10.08;21,742.70,225.38,50.39,10.08;21,839.88,225.38,22.63,10.08;21,542.50,249.48,24.73,10.08;21,599.09,249.48,20.23,10.08;21,664.97,249.48,43.07,10.08;21,742.70,249.48,50.39,10.08;21,837.24,249.48,27.67,10.08;21,542.50,273.60,24.73,10.08;21,599.09,273.60,20.23,10.08;21,657.05,273.60,59.17,10.08;21,736.94,273.60,61.64,10.08;21,837.24,273.60,27.67,10.08;21,546.34,297.70,16.82,10.08;21,599.09,297.70,20.23,10.08;21,658.25,297.70,57.01,10.08;21,736.94,297.70,61.64,10.08;21,837.24,297.70,27.67,10.08;21,542.50,321.77,24.70,10.10;21,601.01,321.77,16.51,10.10;21,670.73,321.77,31.93,10.10;21,751.10,321.77,33.36,10.10;21,837.24,321.77,27.70,10.10;21,542.50,345.91,24.73,10.08;21,601.01,345.91,16.51,10.08;21,667.61,345.91,37.90,10.08;21,751.10,345.91,33.34,10.08;21,837.24,345.91,27.67,10.08;21,542.50,370.01,24.73,10.08;21,601.01,370.01,16.51,10.08;21,662.33,370.01,48.54,10.08;21,751.10,370.01,33.34,10.08;21,837.24,370.01,27.67,10.08;21,590.40,145.39,248.62,12.00;21,74.59,137.19,354.65,13.94;21,44.47,167.71,408.13,10.08;21,44.47,179.71,415.67,10.08;21,44.47,191.69,370.79,10.10;21,216.12,205.15,188.36,11.04;21,216.12,224.11,244.81,10.08;21,229.56,236.09,218.72,10.10;21,229.56,248.14,232.31,10.08;21,229.56,260.14,89.94,10.08;21,216.12,275.26,248.68,10.08;21,229.56,287.24,205.38,10.10;21,212.38,320.04,247.25,11.04;21,212.38,339.02,227.34,10.08;21,225.82,351.02,235.24,10.08;21,225.82,363.02,216.98,10.08;21,212.38,378.14,250.68,10.08;21,225.82,390.12,227.43,10.10;21,225.82,402.17,189.44,10.08;21,225.82,414.17,110.10,10.08;21,36.50,488.12,284.81,7.92;21,531.29,391.27,222.72,9.12;22,36.91,73.64,882.65,13.94;22,36.91,90.48,274.88,13.92;22,36.91,33.84,488.22,24.02;22,78.62,221.69,23.94,12.00;22,257.66,206.45,51.95,12.00;22,247.34,221.55,72.89,12.02;22,247.58,236.95,72.39,12.00;22,421.87,338.40,36.22,12.00;22,412.51,353.52,54.58,12.00;22,66.38,418.70,51.71,12.00;22,238.25,410.64,94.18,12.00;22,257.93,425.76,54.58,12.00;22,159.72,433.85,49.92,12.00;22,165.00,448.23,39.28,12.02;22,166.66,184.28,35.43,12.02;22,154.15,198.72,60.60,12.00;22,139.32,137.88,259.72,13.92;22,425.23,213.84,29.24,12.00;22,412.51,228.96,54.58,12.00;22,641.57,137.88,138.91,13.92;22,537.24,189.38,37.47,13.92;22,532.20,207.17,47.31,13.92;22,543.24,278.98,25.25,13.94;22,542.04,348.98,27.88,13.92;22,535.32,431.05,41.09,13.94;22,614.21,174.96,281.09,10.08;22,614.21,189.36,281.74,10.08;22,614.21,203.76,263.92,10.08;22,614.21,218.14,274.65,10.10;22,614.21,232.58,267.47,10.08;22,614.21,262.54,288.44,10.10;22,614.21,274.58,284.19,10.08;22,614.21,286.58,283.90,10.08;22,614.21,298.58,36.78,10.08;22,614.21,331.75,268.77,10.08;22,614.21,343.75,278.63,10.08;22,614.21,355.75,257.10,10.08;22,614.21,367.75,115.61,10.08;22,74.33,328.03,12.00,34.54;22,74.33,274.47,12.00,50.44;22,36.50,488.12,332.95,7.92;22,392.78,408.07,78.44,10.56;22,392.78,434.98,97.94,10.58;23,45.46,417.10,144.66,11.04;23,45.46,436.32,761.39,11.04;23,45.46,449.52,758.71,11.04;23,45.46,462.72,244.59,11.04;23,36.91,73.64,820.69,13.94;23,36.91,90.48,881.46,13.92;23,36.91,33.84,428.02,24.02;23,243.94,137.19,470.01,13.94;23,46.85,165.15,847.53,10.10;23,46.85,177.19,832.99,10.08;23,46.85,189.19,850.66,10.08;23,46.85,201.19,478.80,10.08;23,349.18,297.65,77.79,11.04;23,70.13,244.80,169.03,10.08;23,70.13,256.80,191.39,10.08;23,69.43,297.91,22.16,11.04;23,167.14,345.70,245.23,10.08;23,165.22,357.70,229.78,10.08;23,165.22,369.70,244.51,10.08;23,165.22,381.68,208.90,10.10;23,349.58,244.56,193.58,10.08;23,349.58,256.56,212.28,10.08;23,349.58,268.56,175.42,10.08;23,505.78,347.62,358.23,10.08;23,505.78,359.62,368.69,10.08;23,505.78,371.60,369.64,10.10;23,505.78,383.64,332.58,10.08;23,625.44,297.91,22.16,11.04;23,168.36,328.54,167.41,10.08;23,511.27,328.87,155.86,10.08;23,355.87,226.42,100.66,10.08;23,628.70,226.42,151.68,10.08;23,623.78,244.08,280.27,10.10;23,623.78,256.13,290.96,10.08;23,623.78,268.13,263.26,10.08;23,623.78,280.13,243.62,10.08;23,75.79,226.42,59.60,10.08;23,505.25,297.24,64.61,11.04;23,166.61,297.65,22.17,11.06"><head/><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="19,36.50,489.97,284.81,7.92;19,36.50,499.57,330.34,7.92">Source: company website, company annual report, public information, Deloitte analysis Remarks: 1. Converted at the annual average exchange rate of USD to RMB in 2021 (1USD = 6.45RMB)</s><s coords="20,36.91,73.64,861.59,13.94;20,36.91,90.48,573.42,13.92;20,36.91,33.84,420.99,24.02;20,86.69,137.19,784.55,13.94;20,44.47,170.62,391.22,10.08">Li-Cycle is working to address the increasing demand for lithium-ion battery materials through innovative recycling solutions and upstream-downstream collaboration and focus on the transformation and sustainable development of global "green energy" Third-party Battery Recyclers: Li-Cycle (1/2)Sound recycling network and innovative and environment-friendly recycling technology promote sustainable, high-quality developmentLi-Cycle, founded in 2016, is a in lithium-ion battery resources recycling leader in North America.</s><s coords="20,437.43,170.62,412.01,10.08">At present, its primary business includes recycling Li-batteries and producing battery-grade materials.</s><s coords="20,850.97,170.62,48.67,10.08;20,44.47,182.60,845.52,10.10;20,102.79,217.75,298.01,12.00;20,42.53,251.28,142.71,10.10;20,55.97,263.33,134.08,10.08;20,55.97,275.33,122.59,10.08;20,55.97,287.33,124.98,10.08;20,55.97,299.31,123.53,10.10;20,55.97,311.35,142.68,10.08;20,55.97,323.35,88.96,10.08;20,42.53,338.47,154.58,10.08;20,55.97,350.47,127.76,10.08;20,55.97,362.50,131.38,10.08;20,55.97,374.50,134.17,10.08;20,55.97,386.50,107.01,10.08;20,55.97,398.50,136.68,10.08;20,55.97,410.48,127.19,10.10;20,55.97,422.52,138.76,10.08;20,55.97,434.52,134.97,10.08;20,55.97,446.52,129.85,10.08;20,240.74,257.64,179.82,10.56;20,500.62,251.52,399.23,10.08;20,500.62,263.50,394.36,10.10;20,500.62,275.54,348.11,10.08;20,519.62,313.56,162.58,10.08;20,510.26,325.68,181.78,10.68;20,539.02,217.75,337.44,12.00;20,733.70,326.30,152.86,9.12;20,733.70,337.13,136.44,9.12;20,733.70,347.93,138.66,9.12;20,733.70,358.73,159.08,9.12;20,733.70,369.53,3.98,9.12;20,307.44,438.77,126.20,9.14;20,36.50,489.97,284.81,7.92;20,36.50,499.57,37.95,7.92">By adopting advanced battery recycling technologies and providing economically-feasible critical battery metals recovery solutions, Li-Cycle offers sustainable products to support the global transition toward electrification KSF 1: Recycling network building around resource channels • Advanced planning: Company's current business growth strategy focuses on North America and Europe, keeping abreast of the increasing demands of leading existing and potential customers of global industrial chain • Deepen cooperation: According to the geographical distribution of each recycling plant, Li-cycle has forged key strategic partnerships across the value chain and completed long-term commercial agreements for in-take and offtake of essential battery materials in each region to further stabilize the recycling and sales channels Li-Cycle North America recycling network Despite the challenges of intensified market competition and increasingly stringent environmental regulations, the environmental benefits of Li-Cycle's proprietary technology can still meet clients' requirements for products quality and sustainability, appealing to ESG devoted clients Environmental benefits comparison for production of 1 tonne of battery materials 1 KSF 2: Environmental-friendly, innovative, differentiated technology Compared with pyrometallurgy, Li-Cycle's technology significantly reduces GHG emissions and avoids the issue of perfluorinated and poly-fluoroalkyl substances (development or newly announced Source: company website, company annual report, public information, Deloitte analysis Remarks: 1.</s><s coords="20,76.29,499.57,213.33,7.92;21,36.91,73.64,854.11,13.94;21,36.91,90.48,291.41,13.92;21,36.91,33.84,420.99,24.02;21,45.82,445.85,522.74,10.08">Compared with direct extraction and refining of natural resources Li-Cycle equipped the closed-loop recycling technology from end-of-life batteries to renewable materials and accelerates the improvement of recovery capacity to achieve vertical integration of resources Third-party Battery Recyclers: Li-Cycle (2/2) • Li-Cycle is actively investing in and building the Spoke and Hub facilities to improve the scale of the battery recycling business.</s><s coords="21,570.57,445.85,333.93,10.08;21,59.26,457.85,221.96,10.08">Li-Cycle is expected to have up to 20 Spoke facilities, 3 ternary lithium battery Hub facilities and 1 LFP lithium battery Hub facility by 2025.</s><s coords="21,283.70,457.85,576.09,10.08;21,224.35,137.19,204.89,13.94;21,44.47,167.71,408.13,10.08;21,44.47,179.71,415.67,10.08;21,44.47,191.69,370.79,10.10;21,216.12,205.15,188.36,11.04;21,216.12,224.11,244.81,10.08;21,229.56,236.09,218.72,10.10;21,229.56,248.14,232.31,10.08;21,229.56,260.14,89.94,10.08;21,216.12,275.26,248.68,10.08;21,229.56,287.24,205.38,10.10;21,212.38,320.04,247.25,11.04;21,212.38,339.02,227.34,10.08;21,225.82,351.02,235.24,10.08;21,225.82,363.02,216.98,10.08;21,212.38,378.14,250.68,10.08;21,225.82,390.12,227.43,10.10;21,225.82,402.17,189.44,10.08;21,225.82,414.17,110.10,10.08;21,36.50,488.12,284.81,7.92;21,531.29,391.27,222.72,9.12;22,36.91,73.64,882.65,13.94;22,36.91,90.48,274.88,13.92;22,36.91,33.84,488.22,24.02;22,78.62,221.69,23.94,12.00;22,712.74,174.96,182.55,10.08;22,614.21,189.36,281.74,10.08;22,614.21,203.76,263.92,10.08;22,614.21,218.14,274.65,10.10;22,614.21,232.58,267.47,10.08;22,614.21,262.54,288.44,10.10;22,614.21,274.58,284.19,10.08;22,614.21,286.58,283.90,10.08;22,614.21,298.58,36.78,10.08;22,614.21,331.75,160.83,10.08">The first Hub facility in Rochester, New York, is projected to have a battery materials processing capacity equivalent to 225,000 EVs every year to cover full battery recycle process Li-Cycle recycles end-of-life batteries to achieve battery full life-cycle coverage through the "Spoke &amp; Hub" network, provides customers with sustainable solutions for lithium-ion batteries, and creates the path to a closed-loop supply chain to support the secondary supply of key battery materials Spoke: Flexible battery processing facility • Recycle and handle the preliminary processing of end-oflife batteries through shredding, separation and other mechanical processes to produce black mass that creates major economic value • The Spoke is a decentralized and flexible-planning facility that processes batteries close to the supply source Hub: Centralized hydrometallurgical processing center • Recover black mass into battery-grade raw materials through hydrometallurgical process for reuse in Li-battery production, including lithium, nickel, cobalt and more • The Hub is a centralized facility for large-scale production of specialty materials that achieve economies of scale in recycling but with a high initial investment and environmental control cost Source: company website, company annual report, public information, Deloitte analysis * Recycling capacity: tonnes of Li-battery equivalent per year Battery manufacturers, as the primary recycler of EV batteries, use their channel advantages to create an industrial closed-loop within the battery life cycle, from collecting and recycling to remanufacturing Business Model: Battery Manufacturer as Recycler OEM as the primary recycler of EV batteries, have arranged the recycling network by establishing subsidiaries, acquiring recycling enterprises, industrial cooperation, etc. to form circular recycling of EV batteries, realize the cost reduction of recycling, and mitigate the bargaining power of upstream raw material suppliers Diversified recycling and resale channels are critical factors for battery manufacturers to effectively control the directional circulation of endof-life batteries and reduce the recycling and reproduction costs of EV batteries Technical restrictions on self-recycling.</s><s coords="22,776.74,331.75,106.24,10.08;22,614.21,343.75,278.63,10.08;22,614.21,355.75,257.10,10.08;22,614.21,367.75,115.61,10.08;22,74.33,328.03,12.00,34.54;22,74.33,274.47,12.00,50.44;22,36.50,488.12,332.95,7.92;22,392.78,408.07,78.44,10.56;22,392.78,434.98,97.94,10.58;23,45.46,417.10,144.66,11.04;23,45.46,436.32,761.39,11.04;23,45.46,449.52,28.21,11.04">Due to the dependence of crucial recycling technologies on recycling enterprises, the operation efficiency of the model is usually low, which further hinders the formation of the scale effect Vehicle dealership Source: CITIC Securities, Everbright Securities, Tianfeng Securities, public information, Deloitte analysis End-of-life battery Production/Sales chain Introduction to Brunp Recycling Guangdong Brunp is one of China's leading high-tech enterprises in the recycling and treatment of end-of-life lithium batteries and producing high-end battery materials in China.</s><s coords="23,75.90,449.52,728.27,11.04;23,45.46,462.72,244.59,11.04;23,36.91,73.64,820.69,13.94;23,36.91,90.48,881.46,13.92;23,36.91,33.84,428.02,24.02;23,243.94,137.19,470.01,13.94;23,46.85,165.15,498.47,10.10">Headquartered in Foshan, Guangdong, Brunp Recycling has set up seven production bases domestic and out of China, including Foshan, Changsha, Pingnan, Fuding, Yichang in China, Morowali and Weda Bay in Indonesia In recent years, CATL has further improved the strategic planning of the company in the lithium battery and new energy industry, give play to the advantages of industrial synergy, and prospectively arranged the recycling business to secure the company's battery materials supply and resources reserve Battery Manufacturers Recycling: CATL (1/2) Prospective planning and industrial cooperation to enhance supply chain security Contemporary Amperex Technology Co., Limited (CATL) is a global leading provider of innovative new energy technologies.</s><s coords="23,547.08,165.15,347.30,10.10;23,46.85,177.19,503.30,10.08">CATL specializes in manufacturing lithium-ion batteries and is committed to providing efficient energy storage solutions for international green-energy applications by leveraging its advanced battery technology.</s><s coords="23,551.91,177.19,327.93,10.08;23,46.85,189.19,55.53,10.08">Since 2015, the company has made prospective planning in battery recycling and regenerating.</s><s coords="23,103.91,189.19,793.60,10.08;23,46.85,201.19,478.80,10.08;23,349.18,297.65,77.79,11.04;23,70.13,244.80,169.03,10.08;23,70.13,256.80,191.39,10.08;23,69.43,297.91,22.16,11.04;23,167.14,345.70,245.23,10.08;23,165.22,357.70,229.78,10.08;23,165.22,369.70,244.51,10.08;23,165.22,381.68,208.90,10.10;23,349.58,244.56,193.58,10.08;23,349.58,256.56,212.28,10.08;23,349.58,268.56,175.42,10.08;23,505.78,347.62,358.23,10.08;23,505.78,359.62,62.98,10.08">Over the years, CATL has participated in recycling technology development and investment in the battery recycling industry by building facilities and cooperating with enterprises, aiming to reduce dependence on upstream resources, ensure the stability of the supply chain, and achieve cost reduction in production September, 2021 Established in 2011, as ATL spun off its EV battery operations into the new company CATL 2011 Acquired 52.88% of the shares of Brunp Recycling, and CATL has planned power battery recycling and regenerating in advance, creating a closed-loop battery industrial chain with complementary upstream-downstream advantages Established a strategic partnership with BASF to expand the European recycling market and promote the recycling business's rapid development The company invested in developing Brunp integrated battery material industrial park in Yichang, Hubei.</s><s coords="23,570.53,359.62,303.94,10.08;23,505.78,371.60,369.64,10.10;23,505.78,383.64,332.58,10.08;23,625.44,297.91,22.16,11.04;23,168.36,328.54,167.41,10.08;23,511.27,328.87,155.86,10.08;23,355.87,226.42,100.66,10.08;23,628.70,226.42,151.68,10.08;23,623.78,244.08,280.27,10.10;23,623.78,256.13,290.96,10.08;23,623.78,268.13,263.26,10.08;23,623.78,280.13,243.62,10.08">The park is an intensive and large-scale production base to support end-oflife battery material recycling, covering the whole battery life cycle, integrating "phosphate mine -raw material -precursor -cathode material -battery recycling" and more 2022 Engaged in recycling by acquiring Brump The strategic planning is taking shape Explored global markets Deepened global business operation CATL signed a tri-party framework agreement with ANTAM and IBI to cooperate on the Indonesia EV battery whole industry chain integration project, which includes nickel laterites mining and processing, EV battery materials, EV battery recycling and remanufacturing</s></p></div></figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_6" coords="24,573.79,207.12,277.75,10.08;24,573.79,231.12,329.98,10.08;24,573.79,243.10,127.18,10.10;24,573.79,258.26,321.82,10.08;24,573.79,270.26,113.69,10.08;24,530.50,206.09,20.41,10.56;24,517.27,231.17,47.11,10.56;24,36.50,488.12,284.81,7.92;24,193.37,309.53,31.35,10.08;24,195.29,320.33,27.79,10.08;24,198.14,253.78,20.57,10.08;24,273.82,309.53,31.35,10.08;24,266.83,320.33,45.50,10.08;24,454.54,367.52,25.45,10.10;24,225.96,367.06,59.40,10.08;24,366.55,367.20,31.71,10.10;24,402.79,273.48,43.71,10.08;24,405.67,286.20,37.82,10.08;24,274.46,248.95,31.35,10.08;24,270.14,261.65,40.25,10.10;24,50.35,274.94,31.35,10.08;24,52.51,285.74,27.22,10.08"><head/><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="24,573.79,207.12,277.75,10.08;24,573.79,231.12,329.98,10.08;24,573.79,243.10,127.18,10.10;24,573.79,258.26,321.82,10.08;24,573.79,270.26,113.69,10.08;24,530.50,206.09,20.41,10.56;24,517.27,231.17,47.11,10.56;24,36.50,488.12,284.81,7.92">Battery recycling: helps to establish industrial ecological closed-loop Resource business: Provides CATL with upstream mineral resources and supports the security of the supply chain Material business: Manufacturing of ternary precursor and other key materials for CATL battery production Core Extensions Source: company website, company annual report, public information, Deloitte analysis</s></p></div></figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_7" coords="25,219.00,169.75,88.46,12.00;25,36.50,488.12,332.95,7.92;25,80.30,357.09,12.00,34.54;25,100.75,349.11,12.00,50.44;25,387.12,420.65,78.44,10.56;25,387.12,447.58,97.94,10.56;26,36.91,73.64,868.49,13.94;26,36.91,90.48,285.58,13.92;26,80.50,415.51,51.74,12.00;26,88.68,430.63,35.44,12.00;26,80.62,208.06,51.71,12.00;26,151.85,384.46,36.27,11.06;26,151.85,397.70,45.10,11.04;26,151.85,410.90,41.95,11.04;26,177.77,137.86,183.14,13.94;26,614.71,137.86,192.71,13.94;26,83.52,325.03,45.66,12.00;26,363.67,348.22,86.29,12.00;26,368.47,363.34,76.81,12.00;26,374.71,378.68,64.33,12.02;26,361.99,413.42,89.70,12.00;26,376.39,428.57,61.27,12.00;26,389.59,443.93,34.57,12.00;26,394.92,326.64,27.10,11.04;26,233.04,200.21,53.30,12.00;26,241.92,215.33,35.16,12.00;26,232.75,251.96,54.77,12.02;26,226.27,267.12,67.51,12.00;26,218.45,175.23,82.30,11.06;26,224.42,355.85,62.32,12.00;26,237.86,370.97,35.44,12.00;26,228.12,421.04,55.96,12.02;26,240.62,436.20,30.97,12.00;26,239.11,326.64,33.80,11.04;26,396.14,200.21,41.65,12.00;26,399.98,215.33,33.98,12.00;26,370.66,175.34,94.43,11.04;26,414.98,262.09,24.24,40.77;26,46.03,440.56,11.04,18.92;26,46.03,404.37,11.04,33.76;26,46.03,361.93,11.04,40.24;26,46.03,321.45,11.04,37.82;26,46.03,294.40,11.04,24.62;26,36.89,33.75,323.86,24.02;26,91.51,246.69,12.00,34.54;26,112.37,238.71,12.00,50.44;26,91.32,360.15,12.00,35.44;26,112.18,368.01,12.00,19.90;26,522.65,323.62,121.40,10.58;26,522.14,179.04,114.05,11.04;26,513.98,201.00,365.71,11.04;26,527.42,214.20,372.22,11.04;26,527.42,227.40,82.72,11.04;26,529.42,250.35,72.58,10.10;26,525.58,262.39,79.93,10.08;26,551.74,274.39,28.16,10.08;26,546.46,286.39,38.41,10.08;26,644.16,248.27,36.22,16.10;26,623.62,266.38,75.82,9.12;26,626.74,277.18,69.35,9.12;26,619.78,287.96,85.11,9.14;26,514.49,347.64,372.06,11.04;26,527.93,360.84,366.76,11.04;26,527.93,374.06,212.22,11.04;26,528.17,389.59,322.61,11.59;26,541.61,403.34,358.35,11.04;26,541.61,419.64,134.34,11.06;26,705.82,419.64,185.47,11.06;26,541.61,432.89,307.63,11.04;26,528.17,448.42,369.95,11.59;26,541.61,462.17,335.27,11.04;26,732.07,248.27,62.37,16.10;26,722.47,271.78,81.73,9.12;26,730.63,282.58,65.11,9.12;26,846.00,248.27,33.40,16.10;26,831.14,266.38,62.51,9.12;26,833.54,277.18,57.82,9.12;26,841.70,287.96,41.47,9.14;26,36.50,488.41,330.77,7.92;27,35.16,222.54,333.62,43.94;27,35.16,275.37,466.73,43.94;28,49.54,299.88,126.31,12.00;28,221.14,299.88,105.68,12.00;28,435.84,299.88,29.77,12.00;28,606.02,299.88,37.00,12.00;28,755.50,299.88,85.75,12.00;28,36.91,73.64,878.17,13.94;28,36.91,90.48,863.30,13.92;28,36.91,107.28,318.06,13.92;28,36.91,33.84,444.18,24.02;28,36.50,488.12,79.33,7.92"><head>••</head><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="25,219.00,169.75,88.46,12.00;25,36.50,488.12,332.95,7.92;25,80.30,357.09,12.00,34.54;25,100.75,349.11,12.00,50.44;25,387.12,420.65,78.44,10.56;25,387.12,447.58,97.94,10.56;26,36.91,73.64,868.49,13.94;26,36.91,90.48,251.05,13.92;26,527.42,201.00,352.27,11.04;26,527.42,214.20,337.93,11.04;26,527.93,347.64,358.62,11.04;26,527.93,360.84,366.76,11.04;26,527.93,374.06,212.22,11.04;26,528.17,389.59,322.61,11.59;26,541.61,403.34,358.35,11.04;26,541.61,419.64,134.34,11.06;26,705.82,419.64,185.47,11.06;26,541.61,432.89,307.63,11.04;26,528.17,448.42,369.95,11.59;26,541.61,462.17,335.27,11.04;26,80.66,488.41,286.61,7.92;28,179.82,73.64,354.62,13.94">Industrial allianceSource: CITIC Securities, Everbright Securities, Tianfeng Securities, public information, Deloitte analysisVehicle dealershipEnd-of-life battery Production/Sales chain Relying on the advantages of core battery technology and battery installation scale, BYD has built its own key industrial chain sectors for battery recycling to complete the closed loop of the industrial Relying on the dramatic increase in sales of self-branded NEV, BYD's EV battery installation is steadily climbing, and its retired battery recycling can reach a BYD has created a complete, end-to-end, and closed-loop industry chain within the industrial ecology of "battery manufacturing -vehicle manufacturing -battery recycling -evaluation and screening -recycling" -For recycling channels, BYD has a nationwide recycling network of 51 specialized battery recycling sites and authorized dealers for retired EV batteries For evaluation and screening, Baolong factory dismantles and evaluates retired batteries, and adopts suitable methods for batteries recycling -For recycling, BYD Huizhou is responsible for recycling cathode materials, and in addition, it reached a strategic collaboration with GEM in 2015 on recycling Securities, Everbright Securities, Tianfeng Securities, CPCA, CAICV, GGII, Deloitte analysis market mechanism challenges coexist in the recycling industry.</s><s coords="28,538.83,73.64,376.26,13.94;28,36.91,90.48,181.46,13.92">Thus, many problems are still to be solved in each sector of the EV battery recycling industry chain.</s><s coords="28,221.80,90.48,678.41,13.92;28,36.91,107.28,318.06,13.92;28,36.91,33.84,444.18,24.02;28,36.50,488.12,79.33,7.92">The healthy development of the EV battery recycling market is in urgent need of the guidance of macro policies and the joint efforts of all individual parties in the industry chain Challenge-facing EV battery recycling industry Source: Deloitte analysis</s></p></div></figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" coords="1,286.08,53.76,385.44,385.68"><head/><label/><figDesc><div><p/></div></figDesc><graphic coords="1,286.08,53.76,385.44,385.68" type="bitmap"/></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" coords="21,511.20,129.36,413.34,283.26"><head/><label/><figDesc><div><p/></div></figDesc><graphic coords="21,511.20,129.36,413.34,283.26" type="bitmap"/></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_0" coords="5,318.46,180.02,326.02,269.72"><head>Korea Regulate the industry from the legislative level</head><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="6,36.91,73.64,846.67,13.94;6,36.91,90.48,416.29,13.92;6,36.91,33.84,484.16,24.02;7,36.91,73.64,814.09,13.94;7,36.91,90.48,857.63,13.92;7,36.91,107.28,453.86,13.92;7,36.91,31.98,685.83,28.10">The development of the global EV battery recycling market is about to accelerate, which is expected to exceed 10 billion dollars in the next five years, among which the recycling market of the lithium is the most considerable Global EV Battery Recycling Market Size Prospects After years of development, battery recycling policies and legislation in developed countries are complete with stricter requirements; China has significantly accelerated the introduction of battery recycling policies over the past decade, aiming to promote and ensure the construction of recycling systems and guide the standardized and integrated development of the industry EV Battery Recycling Market Drivers -Macro Policy Guidance</s></p></div></figDesc><table coords="5,318.46,180.02,326.02,269.72"><row><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell cols="6">Global EV battery recycling market size projection 1</cell></row><row><cell>Billion USD 2 Ni Li</cell><cell>Co</cell><cell>Mn</cell><cell>+81%</cell><cell>100 200 300 400</cell><cell cols="6">Global lithium supply 9.1 Japan &amp; South Interim Measures for the Management of Global lithium demand 63% -37% Vehicle Power Battery 63% 19.1 26.6 13.5 35.7 46.5 +38% Recovery and Utilization of New Energy Comprehensive Utilization in Industry in 2020 Accelerating the Promotion of Comprehensive Utilization of Industrial Resources Implementation Plan for Industrial Carbon Key Points of Energy Conservation and Dioxide Peaking</cell></row><row><cell>0.8</cell><cell/><cell>3.4 71%</cell><cell>67% 4.7</cell><cell cols="2">2022E 2023E 61% 6.0</cell><cell>2024E 2025E 62%</cell><cell>2026E</cell><cell>2027E 2028E 62%</cell><cell>2029E 62% 2030E</cell><cell>63%</cell></row><row><cell>2021</cell><cell/><cell>2022E</cell><cell>2023E</cell><cell>2024E</cell><cell/><cell>2025E</cell><cell/><cell>2026E</cell><cell>2027E</cell><cell>2028E</cell><cell>2029E</cell><cell>2030E</cell></row></table><note coords="6,36.50,486.49,222.22,7.92;6,36.50,498.25,681.45,7.92;7,36.50,488.12,285.19,7.92"><p><s coords="6,36.50,486.49,222.22,7.92;6,36.50,498.25,681.45,7.92">Source: Anson Securities, Wind, public information, Deloitte analysis Remarks: 1. Estimate based on the theoretical recyclable quantity and price of lithium, nickel, cobalt and manganese; 2. Converted at the annual average exchange rate of USD to RMB in 2021 (1USD = 6.45RMB)</s><s coords="7,36.50,488.12,285.19,7.92">Source: government website, Everbright Securities, public information, Deloitte analysis</s></p></note></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_2" coords="7,41.50,291.06,508.11,185.26"><head/><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="8,36.91,33.84,869.11,24.02;8,36.91,73.64,831.85,13.94;8,36.91,90.48,853.03,13.92;8,36.91,107.28,621.29,13.92">Driving Factor of Battery Recycling Market: The Upcoming Trend of EV Battery RetirementThe retirement tide of EV batteries has promoted the gradual release of recyclable battery waste and driven the development of the global lithium recycling market, with the volume of end-of-life batteries and process scraps rising at a CAGR of 43% over the next decade; The Chinese market, which leads the global EV market, is also expected to usher in considerable growth in the field of Li-battery recycling</s></p></div></figDesc><table coords="7,41.50,291.06,508.11,185.26"><row><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell>Global EV battery installation shares in 2021</cell></row><row><cell cols="2">End-of-life Li-battery</cell><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell>1,483</cell></row><row><cell cols="3">Li-battery process scraps</cell><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell cols="3">Cathode process scraps</cell><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell>1,119</cell><cell/></row><row><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell>+43%</cell><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell>840</cell><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell cols="2">Clean Air Conservation Act 621</cell><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell>453</cell><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell>61</cell><cell>104</cell><cell>156</cell><cell>227</cell><cell>325</cell><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell>2021</cell><cell>2022E</cell><cell>2023E</cell><cell>2024E</cell><cell>2025E</cell><cell>2026E</cell><cell>2027E</cell><cell>2028E</cell><cell>2029E</cell><cell>2030E</cell></row><row><cell cols="3">Makes regulations for the types of waste</cell><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell cols="3">recycling, disposal methods, cost, etc. to</cell><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell cols="3">encourage all parties in the industry chain to collaborate to help properly recycle batteries</cell><cell/><cell/><cell/><cell cols="3">The Law for Promotion of Effective Utilization of Resources in Japan</cell><cell/></row></table></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_3" coords="8,36.50,137.18,882.10,368.99"><head>The projection of global recyclable end-of-life Li-batteries and battery production scraps 52.1%</head><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="9,74.32,73.64,637.87,13.94">and direct recycle are the most generally acceptable and environmentally friendly methods of batteries disposal.</s><s coords="9,715.61,73.64,168.37,13.94;9,36.91,90.48,683.32,13.92">Large-scale applications of EV battery reuse is challenging, and EV battery recycling might be dominated by direct recycle in the medium and long term</s></p></div></figDesc><table coords="8,830.90,333.98,87.71,40.83"><row><cell>Recycling Methods of EV Battery</cell></row><row><cell>Reuse application</cell></row><row><cell>China's EV battery</cell></row><row><cell>installation</cell></row><row><cell>154.5 GWh</cell></row></table><note coords="8,172.68,228.49,4.02,7.92;8,662.66,187.37,135.66,12.00;8,662.66,168.98,27.34,12.00;8,36.50,486.49,422.97,7.92;8,36.50,498.25,242.24,7.92;9,36.91,73.64,34.05,13.94"><p><s coords="8,172.68,228.49,4.02,7.92;8,662.66,187.37,135.66,12.00;8,662.66,168.98,27.34,12.00;8,36.50,486.49,422.97,7.92;8,36.50,498.25,242.24,7.92;9,36.91,73.64,34.05,13.94">1 Other countries and regions China Source: SNE Research, China Automotive Battery Innovation Alliance, Wind, Anson Securities, public information, Deloitte analysis Remarks: 1. Converted to the amount of EV batteries that can be producedReuse</s></p></note></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_4" coords="9,36.48,137.48,837.91,357.29"><head>Reuse: utilization of the residual capacity of battery Recycle: recovery of metal materials and other resources</head><label/><figDesc/><table coords="9,36.48,486.85,197.68,7.92"><row><cell>Source: CAAM, Anson Securities, public information, Deloitte</cell></row></table></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_5" coords="9,42.98,192.08,413.42,302.69"><head>analysis Recycling methods Pros Cons -Applicable limitations: not</head><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="9,213.62,405.26,242.78,11.04;9,91.20,417.26,262.62,11.04;9,77.76,432.14,5.60,11.04">suitable for ternary (NMC) lithium battery, difficulty to maintain economies of scale subject to many qualifications -</s></p></div></figDesc><table/></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_6" coords="9,77.76,182.98,379.10,286.87"><head>Inefficiency: The evaluation process of batteries is time-consuming and inefficient -Potential safety risks: The</head><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="9,210.74,446.77,235.11,11.06;9,91.20,458.81,326.68,11.04">internal safety hazards of retired batteries are highly concealed, which affects the remaining life and safety of the battery pack</s></p></div></figDesc><table coords="9,172.94,182.98,72.47,103.44"><row><cell>Inspection, Data</cell></row><row><cell>evaluation</cell></row><row><cell>Properties</cell></row><row><cell>detection</cell></row><row><cell>Resistance</cell></row><row><cell>determination</cell></row></table></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_7" coords="9,292.58,169.01,609.40,116.85"><head>Reusable pack Reusable module Reusable cell Recycle Anode materials</head><label/><figDesc/><table coords="9,582.55,169.01,319.43,71.06"><row><cell/><cell>Cathode materials</cell></row><row><cell>Graphite, silicon-based materials</cell><cell>Lithium, cobalt, nickel, manganese and other metal oxides, recycled</cell></row><row><cell/><cell>by direct method and</cell></row><row><cell/><cell>extractive metallurgy</cell></row></table></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_8" coords="9,94.78,213.50,365.93,100.01"><head>• End-of-life battery</head><label/><figDesc/><table coords="9,399.84,215.76,60.87,72.37"><row><cell>Reuse: Development Limitation Factors</cell></row><row><cell>The reuse industry has significant development limitations and bottlenecks at the current stage. The downstream application development is expected to</cell></row><row><cell>be slow before the policy system is improved and the industry standard is established</cell></row><row><cell>Energy storage</cell></row><row><cell>Low-speed</cell></row><row><cell>vehicles</cell></row><row><cell>UPS</cell></row><row><cell>Source: government website, public information, Deloitte analysis</cell></row></table></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_9" coords="10,45.62,436.46,869.13,35.76"><head>The current market situation: the</head><label/><figDesc><div><p><s coords="10,192.99,436.46,258.91,10.56">current commercialization cases of EV battery reuse are few.</s><s coords="10,454.29,436.46,460.47,10.56;10,45.62,448.94,403.10,10.56">Most of the projects are pilot programs, with only a few regular enterprises with qualifications participating, such as GEM, China Tower, etc.; the current reuse market is not yet standardized and in chaos.</s><s coords="10,450.86,448.94,455.74,10.56;10,45.62,461.66,561.74,10.56">Market confusion caused by non-compliant small workshops forces the regular enterprises into a dilemma, which makes the market less attractive to enterprises that have not entered, and the market is difficult to scale up in the short term</s></p></div></figDesc><table/></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_10" coords="10,162.00,130.20,689.07,254.68"><head>Policy Factor Market Factor Technology Factor Small workshops</head><label/><figDesc/><table coords="10,426.98,301.58,94.89,83.30"><row><cell>Collection</cell></row><row><cell>No hazardous waste</cell></row><row><cell>management qualification;</cell></row><row><cell>No invoicing required</cell></row><row><cell>No inspection/environmental</cell></row><row><cell>treatment;</cell></row><row><cell>Low production line input</cell></row></table></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_11" coords="10,446.26,153.70,462.93,226.77"><head>Reuse Low cost High efficiency • Key technologies to be broken through, industry standards to be established: The</head><label/><figDesc/><table coords="10,656.50,164.50,252.69,204.14"><row><cell cols="3">battery life-cycle traceability management and</cell></row><row><cell cols="3">industry-standard system are to be established, and technical</cell></row><row><cell cols="3">problems still exist in several sectors of the reuse technology process</cell></row><row><cell cols="3">Evaluation and sorting -Battery specifications are complex, and life</cell></row><row><cell>evaluation is difficult</cell><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell cols="3">Detection and screening -Lack of battery use records, complicated</cell></row><row><cell>detecting technology</cell><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell cols="3">Restructuring -High technical barriers to battery consistency</cell></row><row><cell>management</cell><cell/><cell/></row><row><cell cols="3">Product certification -For the formation of industry standards,</cell></row><row><cell cols="2">product certification is difficult</cell><cell/></row><row><cell>Collection</cell><cell>Evaluation &amp; Sorting</cell><cell>Disassembly</cell></row><row><cell>Certification</cell><cell>Restructuring</cell><cell>Detection &amp; Screening</cell></row></table></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" type="table" xml:id="tab_14" coords="24,516.10,181.75,385.70,188.86"><head>000 tonnes/year 99.3% 90% Total battery recycling capacity Recovery rate of Ni, Co and Mn Recovery rate of Li</head><label/><figDesc/><table/><note coords="24,516.10,298.49,385.70,10.58;24,529.54,311.02,121.82,10.56;24,534.70,331.57,30.32,16.08;24,516.10,181.75,312.73,10.56"><p><s coords="24,516.10,298.49,385.70,10.58;24,529.54,311.02,121.82,10.56;24,534.70,331.57,30.32,16.08;24,516.10,181.75,312.73,10.56">• The existing resource recycling capacity and key metal recovery rate of Brunp Recycling stand among the top in Asia:120,• Brunp's "One core and Two extensions" boost CATL's circular business</s></p></note></figure>
			<note xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" place="foot" xml:id="foot_0" coords="4,36.91,510.08,126.50,6.48"><p><s coords="4,36.91,510.08,21.97,6.48">© 2022.</s><s coords="4,59.92,510.08,103.49,6.48">For information, contact Deloitte China.</s></p></note>
		</body>
		<back>

			<div type="acknowledgement">
<div><head coords="33,36.96,383.66,106.61,13.92">Acknowledgments</head><p><s coords="33,36.96,413.14,843.09,12.00;33,36.96,427.54,331.52,12.00;33,36.96,447.00,4.20,11.26;33,59.54,446.74,218.05,12.00;33,36.96,464.30,4.20,11.26;33,59.54,464.04,218.09,12.00">We would like to take this opportunity to express our heartfelt appreciation to all colleagues of <rs type="institution">Deloitte Consulting China</rs> who supported this study, with special thanks to the following colleagues for their significant contributions to this report: • <rs type="person">Chris Lu</rs>, <rs type="affiliation">Deloitte Consulting China</rs>, Manager • Neil Kong, Deloitte Consulting China, Analyst</s></p></div>
			</div>			<div type="annex">
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="33,36.91,33.84,105.22,24.02">Contact Us</head></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="33,85.06,241.72,80.19,18.00">Andy Zhou</head><p><s coords="33,90.58,268.30,69.12,12.00;33,56.98,282.70,136.18,12.00;33,52.90,317.52,144.47,12.00">Deloitte China Automotive Industry Leader lingkunzhou@deloitte.com.cn</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="33,555.12,241.64,76.07,18.00">Terry Wen</head><p><s coords="33,531.58,268.20,123.29,12.02;33,573.60,282.65,39.44,12.00;33,537.60,317.43,111.39,12.02">Deloitte Consulting China Director zwen@deloitte.com.cn</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="33,781.32,241.55,91.07,18.02">Mavis Wang</head><p><s coords="33,765.24,268.18,123.12,12.00;33,781.80,282.58,90.26,12.00;33,758.52,317.40,136.80,12.00">Deloitte Consulting China Assistant Manager maviwang@deloitte.com.cn</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="33,313.01,241.72,91.26,18.00">Steve Cheng</head><p><s coords="33,297.17,268.30,123.12,12.00;33,340.61,282.70,36.31,12.00;33,298.85,317.52,119.78,12.00">Deloitte Consulting China Partner scheng@deloitte.com.cn</s></p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head coords="34,37.34,302.99,51.89,8.88">About Deloitte</head><p><s coords="34,37.34,313.79,502.18,8.88">Deloitte refers to one or more of Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu Limited ("DTTL"), its global network of member firms, and their related entities.</s><s coords="34,542.39,313.79,169.09,8.88;34,37.34,324.61,352.75,8.88">DTTL (also referred to as "Deloitte Global") and each of its member firms and their affiliated entities are legally separate and independent entities.</s><s coords="34,392.95,324.61,148.46,8.88">DTTL does not provide services to clients.</s><s coords="34,544.03,324.61,129.45,8.88">Please see www.deloitte.com/about</s><s coords="34,676.63,324.61,27.63,8.88;34,37.34,335.41,21.13,8.88">to learn more.</s></p><p><s coords="34,37.34,354.13,327.29,8.88">Deloitte Asia Pacific Limited is a company limited by guarantee and a member firm of DTTL.</s><s coords="34,367.01,354.13,337.74,8.88;34,37.34,364.93,648.49,8.88;34,37.34,375.76,239.87,8.88">Members of Deloitte Asia Pacific Limited and their related entities, each of which are separate and independent legal entities, provide services from more than 100 cities across the region, including Auckland, Bangkok, Beijing, Hanoi, Hong Kong, Jakarta, Kuala Lumpur, Manila, Melbourne, Osaka, Shanghai, Singapore, Sydney, Taipei and Tokyo.</s></p><p><s coords="34,37.34,394.48,340.55,8.88">The Deloitte brand entered the China market in 1917 with the opening of an office in Shanghai.</s><s coords="34,380.75,394.48,312.03,8.88;34,37.34,405.28,391.56,8.88">Today, Deloitte China delivers a comprehensive range of audit &amp; assurance, consulting, financial advisory, risk advisory and tax services to local, multinational and growth enterprise clients in China.</s><s coords="34,431.29,405.28,241.49,8.88;34,37.34,416.08,396.74,8.88">Deloitte China has also made-and continues to make-substantial contributions to the development of China's accounting standards, taxation system and professional expertise.</s><s coords="34,436.94,416.08,263.22,8.88;34,37.34,426.86,110.81,8.90">Deloitte China is a locally incorporated professional services organization, owned by its partners in China.</s><s coords="34,150.52,426.86,447.32,8.90;34,37.34,437.70,145.00,8.88">To learn more about how Deloitte makes an Impact that Matters in China, please connect with our social media platforms at www2.deloitte.com/cn/en/social-media.</s></p><p><s coords="34,37.34,456.42,667.93,8.88;34,37.34,467.22,38.87,8.88">This communication is for internal distribution and use only among personnel of Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu Limited, its member firms, and their related entities (collectively, the "Deloitte Network").</s><s coords="34,78.59,467.22,480.15,8.88">None of the Deloitte Network shall be responsible for any loss whatsoever sustained by any person who relies on this communication.</s></p></div>			</div>
			<div type="references">

				<listBibl/>
			</div>
		</back>
	</text>
</TEI>